<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Somebody Please Help Me</title>
    <link>https://juliusreade.com/tags/paleo/index.xml</link>
    <description>Recent content on Somebody Please Help Me</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>This work is licensed under a Creative Commons Attribution-ShareAlike 4.0 International License.</copyright>
    <atom:link href="https://juliusreade.com/tags/paleo/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>Why The Paleo Diet Isn&#39;t Bullshit</title>
      <link>https://juliusreade.com/2017/05/14/why-the-paleo-diet-isnt-bullshit/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 May 2017 11:33:26 +1100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://juliusreade.com/2017/05/14/why-the-paleo-diet-isnt-bullshit/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;!--
I eat paleo and here&#39;s why I&#39;m not crazy.
Why the paleo diet isn&#39;t bullshit. 

--&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I think the paleo diet is brilliant.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;ve been eating paleo on and off for approximately five years, remaining entirely paleo for the past two.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It&amp;rsquo;s brilliant because I&amp;rsquo;m a health fanatic, and it helps me maintain that quite easily.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I suppose I&amp;rsquo;m writing this article because of all the mixed, and largely negative ideas of what the paleo diet actually is.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In part, because of the intense transformation that takes place on someone&amp;rsquo;s face, the moment you tell them you eat paleo.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Almost as if they&amp;rsquo;ve just discovered someone&amp;rsquo;s been inappropiately touching their children.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It&amp;rsquo;s terrifying.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;!--There&#39;s something intense that changes within a person when you tell them you eat paleo. 

In the same sense that there&#39;s a bit of a taboo surrounding the underground gambling circuit or touching other people&#39;s children. --&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Many people view the paleo diet as this hilarious market-driven gimmick, that abtains to running around naked, beating people with a club like an ancient caveman.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Perhaps even as the natural evolutional trend to scientology.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Which baffles me, because the diet makes sense from both scientifically and nutritionally.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;However, that&amp;rsquo;s aside from the point, because humans will always stoop to the lowest common demoninator.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Oh wait, Trump got elected?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Go figure.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Ultimately, I think there are two issues at play here.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Firstly, I think we inherently distrust fanatics.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And of course, it takes a fanatic to want to do the whole paleo thing in the first place, which really doesn&amp;rsquo;t help.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Because fanatics are viewed as a kind of unholy disease, rather than a source of truth.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Especially when it comes to health and diets.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And when everyone has an opinion, yours is always the wrong one.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Secondly, and perhaps most influentially, is the connotation the paleo diet has with the paleolithic period.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Put simply, here&amp;rsquo;s how it usually goes down when I try to explain the paleo diet:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;So the paleo blah, blah, blah, blah, blah blah blah blah.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Because once you mention the word &amp;lsquo;paleo&amp;rsquo;, you can literally see their brain shut off and enter into a kind of droopy fantasy-land.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Every word you speak following that specific word becomes nothing more than biological soup to them.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;At that point, they&amp;rsquo;ve already happily generalised absolutely everything they&amp;rsquo;re willing to know about you.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;Ah, that dickhead. I bet he uses a spear instead of fork. Poor bugger.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is frustating because the paleo diet has very little, if almost nothing to do with the paleolithic period.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It really is nothing more than a cheap reference, like what pineapples have to do with apples.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Oh, and let&amp;rsquo;s not even get started on this word &amp;lsquo;diet&amp;rsquo; which already raises strong suspicion well beyond the scope of this article.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So here I am, hoping to explain the whole paleo thing to you, and why you may not get it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In particular, I want to go into the kind of lifestyle it promotes, as well as the kinds of people it inherently attracts.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Because I promise I don&amp;rsquo;t touch other people&amp;rsquo;s children.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Well&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;health-fanatic-ewwwwwww&#34;&gt;Health Fanatic? Ewwwwwww.&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://juliusreade.com/img/blog/14-01.png&#34; alt=&#34;Health Fanatic? Ewwwwwww.&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I suppose there&amp;rsquo;s a very simple question I would pose to anyone.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Is it such a bad thing to be fanatic about your health?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A lot of people think that the whole paleo thing is taking it a bit too far.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;On the contrary, I think heart disease and obesity is taking it too far.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Of course, the point of difference is that non-paleo folk don&amp;rsquo;t believe that their diets contribute towards these things.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Hence the point of contention.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Regardless, allow me to try and explain why a lot of us paleo folk do it anyway.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And for the sake of argument, let&amp;rsquo;s just assume that it&amp;rsquo;s good for you.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Not eating processed foods, excess sugar and meeting all your nutritional requirements surely can&amp;rsquo;t be a bad thing, right?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You cunning Nazi.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Certainly, I want to start off by saying that we don&amp;rsquo;t hate food.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We love our bread and butter just as much as anyone else, and by gosh, do we think it tastes great.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It&amp;rsquo;s just that we care that little bit more about our health instead.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Which really is to say that we have different priorities about what we believe will make us happier in the long run.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Many of us paleo folk believe that being able to function will make us happier in the long run, than having access to the simple pleasures of bread.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And of course, there are plenty of amazingly delicious paleo dishes out there too, so it&amp;rsquo;s not like we&amp;rsquo;re starving ourselves either.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So why this emphasis on function?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Well, in my particular case it&amp;rsquo;s two-fold:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;At the end of the day, I just want to achieve my goals and ambitions and get shit done.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And not being able to function to the fullest of my ability greatly affects my physical and mental health, which trickles down to my ability to pursue my goals.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Which when you&amp;rsquo;re already suffering from mental health issues, is difficult enough as is without eating as healthily as possible to regulate how you feel.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Basically, it becomes very difficult to do anything, let alone prevent mental breakdowns when you&amp;rsquo;re feeling bloated or your energy levels aren&amp;rsquo;t consistent.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And perhaps, some might argue, poor diets are the inherent cause of depression and  mental illness (look into the correlation between gut bacteria and depresison).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So that&amp;rsquo;s the why, however the reason behind the paleo diet is so much more pervasive than that.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Obviously, this kind of regime attracts a certain kind of person which society largely loathes anyway.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Excessively productive, ambitious and highly insecure individuals.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Those fucking twats.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Again, we love cake just as much as anyone else, it&amp;rsquo;s just we love the idea of becoming a multi-millionaire more.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Yes, I know it&amp;rsquo;s not sexy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And that&amp;rsquo;s ultimately why the movement was doomed to remain an obscure niche for those who need it to pursue their greed.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It&amp;rsquo;s part of what drums up this me vs them mentality.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I suppose this is why the paleo diet is often compared to religion - as this bohemoth, &amp;lsquo;you shall not pass&amp;rsquo; ideology, where there is one way, and one way only.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Which is true, because in our case, our one and only way is success - and we will stop at nothing to obtain it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Because there is nothing we hate more than those more successful than us.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I feel it. You feel it. We all feel it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I suppose there&amp;rsquo;s a fatal flaw in thinking that paleo is about making everyone healthy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In reality, it&amp;rsquo;s about exploiting those who are unhealthy, in order to be more productive and to beat the competition down.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;the-science-behind-the-paleo-diet&#34;&gt;The Science Behind The Paleo Diet&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://juliusreade.com/img/blog/14-02.png&#34; alt=&#34;The Science Behind The Paleo Diet&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As for what the diet actually is, I suppose there are two points that stand out:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The first point relates the range of foods that the diet deems appropiate to eat.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is the aspect people focus on most, and is perhaps the least important point.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The other aspect is the macro-nutrient content of the diet - which is ultimately what matters when considering any diet.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;hellip;and arguably has nothing directly to do with the paleo diet at all.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In a nutshell, here is what is wrong with most modern diets, from a macro-nutrient point of view:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Put simply, most of us are eating too much sugar and carbohydrates, provided our modern lifestyles.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Why?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Two reasons:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Most people believe in this hiliarious concept called &amp;lsquo;moderation&amp;rsquo;, despite sugar being an inherently addictive substance.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Secondly, the bastardisation and now wide-spread belief that fat is evil, even though it&amp;rsquo;s not.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The primary reason why sugar/carbs are bad is because they&amp;rsquo;re an awful source of sustainable energy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;They burn quickly, meaning you must consistently eat more sugar to maintain your energy levels.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Which in reality, given the inherent lack of self-control most of us exhibit, along with the addictive qualities of sugar, leads to over-eating.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And as excess sugar readily converts into fat (unlike fat consumption, which does not), is a recipe for disaster.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So there&amp;rsquo;s ya problem.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now the alternative to a high-sugar diet is to instead rely on a high-fat diet (somewhat related to the process of ketosis), as fat makes for an excellent source of sustainable energy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Not only does it prevent cravings by making us feel full, however it&amp;rsquo;s also a slow burning source of energy - meaning you don&amp;rsquo;t need to eat as much to feel full.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Perfect.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The only issue is that in order to gear your body towards effectively metabolising fat as a primary source of energy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You must ensure that you keep your sugar/carb intake to an absolute minimum, in addition to increasing your fat intake.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And guess what?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Most modern diets make this entirely impossible.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Not only are there few modern foods/meals today that are a high quality source of fat.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;However given most staples involve either wheat and rice - you&amp;rsquo;re basically doomed for failure.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is where the paleo diet comes in.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It&amp;rsquo;s restrictive and that&amp;rsquo;s the point.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It&amp;rsquo;s a guideline that allows you to eat high-fat and low-carb, by simply sticking to the foods we consider &amp;lsquo;paleo&amp;rsquo; foods.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In addition, you also avoid all the other shit like gluten, lectins and phytates - which relates back to our first point.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;That certain foods are inherently destructive to human biology.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I won&amp;rsquo;t explore these ideas in detail, because I feel it&amp;rsquo;s less important (though still very important) than compared to explaining the importance of macro-nutrient intake.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Listen, if you&amp;rsquo;re eating the right macro-nutrient ratios, then you&amp;rsquo;re going to have success with your health.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It&amp;rsquo;s just the paleo diet makes it easier, because it&amp;rsquo;s already built-in and cuts down on making those decisions.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;paleo-vs-moderation&#34;&gt;Paleo vs Moderation&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://juliusreade.com/img/blog/14-03.png&#34; alt=&#34;Paleo vs Moderation&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Interestingly, and perhaps why so many people have come to fear the diet.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Is because the paleo diet stands, quite literally, opposite to the general view of moderation.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It goes against this wide-spread belief in society that it&amp;rsquo;s okay to moderate.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Instead, what it proposes is restriction - which let&amp;rsquo;s be honest, is probably what most of us need.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Certainly, it&amp;rsquo;s how I deal with a lot of my addictions and flaws, by completely restricting myself from my vices.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So why should our diets be any different?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It&amp;rsquo;s the reason why things like routine and consistency work so well.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Because humans are inherently emotional creatures that need structure and logic in their lives to function in society.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Otherwise we wouldn&amp;rsquo;t need laws or timetables.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I suppose the great irony of the paleo diet is that it&amp;rsquo;s incredibly suited for those who aren&amp;rsquo;t fanatic about their health, as it makes dieting so easy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Yet on the otherhand it takes a fanatic to want to do it within the first place.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The reason why it&amp;rsquo;s easy and sustainable, is because it helps prevent cravings.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And it takes the choice and anxiety out of choosing what we must eat next.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In the paleo diet you literally do not need to think or worry.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;All you have to do is stick to a range of foods, and the rest will sort itself out. It&amp;rsquo;s that simple.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The problem however has never been with the paleo diet.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It has been with the attitude us people have had towards health.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In essence, it means that the less crazy you are with your health, the more inversely difficult it will be to become healthy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Not only will you be less committed mentally, however the diet you&amp;rsquo;ll be approaching will be less effective.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Due in part to your own self-limiting beliefs of what you believe may work as a diet, in order to satisfy your own beliefs.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Which is also to say that if you&amp;rsquo;re not dedicated to your health, then you&amp;rsquo;re going to fail no matter what you do.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It&amp;rsquo;s the reason most diets fail.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I suppose it&amp;rsquo;s like those people who try to lose weight by doing the whole shake thing, yet they also refuse to exercise.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It&amp;rsquo;s what a lot of people, yet it does nothing to control cravings or even promote future healthy eating choices.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The initiative simply isn&amp;rsquo;t there.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;it-just-works&#34;&gt;It. Just. Works.&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://juliusreade.com/img/blog/14-04.png&#34; alt=&#34;It. Just. Works.&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You know, there&amp;rsquo;s also a very good reason why people do the paleo diet.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It just works.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Ever since eating paleo, I don&amp;rsquo;t crash or slow down nearly as much as I used to.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I wake up at 5:43am each working day, and I blaze until 9pm at night.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I mean, yes. I still get immensely bored at work and there are times where I just cbf everything and want to sleep all day.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;However I couldn&amp;rsquo;t possibly imagine how much worse it would be if I didn&amp;rsquo;t have all this extra energy from my diet.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Even after all that, I still manage to find the energy to lift weights at 7:20pm after work, three times a week for an hour.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;m focused. I&amp;rsquo;m full of energy and my brain is literally go, go, go.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You know that drowziness you get around 5:30pm on the train-ride home?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I don&amp;rsquo;t get that anymore.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I think the interesting thing is that you don&amp;rsquo;t realise how bad something is until you understand why and become aware of it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I remember prior to the paleo diet I used to have trouble shitting for years, and I would frequently get mouth ulcers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But you just assume that it&amp;rsquo;s normal.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You assume that this is the normal, human experience and I think this is part of the reason why people distrust the paleo diet.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We&amp;rsquo;re so stuck within our own paradigm, that we don&amp;rsquo;t realise that there&amp;rsquo;s so much more out there.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It&amp;rsquo;s sort of like the culture shock of when you visit another country, or when you work for a buisness for the first time and you finally understand what all the fuss is about.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;People don&amp;rsquo;t realise that they could have so much more energy, because they think they don&amp;rsquo;t realise that it&amp;rsquo;s possible.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Of course, the issue is that you have to experience it before you can realise it, and this is the reason most people will never change.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You cannot know until you commit, and people are afraid of committing, hence the term &amp;lsquo;average&amp;rsquo;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Most people are average, myself included.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Rather, it&amp;rsquo;s what you choose to do with it that defines who you are.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;i-m-not-trying-to-touch-your-children&#34;&gt;I&amp;rsquo;m Not Trying To Touch Your Children&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://juliusreade.com/img/blog/14-05.png&#34; alt=&#34;I&#39;m Not Trying To Touch Your Children&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The worst part is how defensive people get when you mention the paleo diet, as if you&amp;rsquo;re attacking their way of life.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As if there&amp;rsquo;s something inherently immoral, almost disgusting about having a different nutritional opinion.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As if I&amp;rsquo;m trying to sabotage the progress of the human race.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It&amp;rsquo;s absolutely terrifying.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;At the end of the day, it’s a numbers game.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We have more fat, obese, unhealthy, sugar-addled people today than we do people willing to do something about it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So rather than target them, we instead find ourselves ridiculing those who are challenging the status quo.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Perhaps that is the problem with society - our current inability to say things for what they are, due to the repurcussions of other people&amp;rsquo;s self-limiting beliefs.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You know, because apparently it’s their ‘choice’ to have a tray of donuts for breakfast.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Yet myself on the other hand, am significantly deluded for thinking there&amp;rsquo;s anything positive in having a steak instead.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Yet when it comes to those who are actually doing something about their health, they are ridiculed.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;They are ridiculed for trying too hard.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;However, I will say this.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I think I understand how religious people feel about persecution over their own beliefs.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And that&amp;rsquo;s okay too, because this is the world we live in - and your claim is what you can get away with.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Which in my case, is a healthy body and a self-determination that goes beyond these wods.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I think I&amp;rsquo;m doing just fine.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;!--


Just sayin&#39;, you never see a fat person eat paleo, even if they may be an asshole. 


Most people still believe in the two-party system, some form of god and a whole number of fallacies which would be enough to sedate an entire village. 

However that&#39;s also aside from the point. 


Instead, I think the reason for reigns much deeper than merely &#39;the facts&#39; or our own individual beliefs. 






The funny thing is when people report that it makes them feel like shit.

When they already have been feeling like shit the entire time anyway. 



This is on top of all the inherently bad things in existing non-paleo foods, such as 







You know, you can rip the bandaid off, or you can teeter it slowly until it you eventually whimper at the prickle of your skin hair. 

That&#39;s entirely your choice.


Of course, most of us aren&#39;t, due to the range of modern foods we 



The problem is that most modern foods and diets make it incredibly difficult to do so. 

Most Western diets are 


I eat paleo and here&#39;s why I&#39;m not crazy.




--&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>