<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Depression on Julius Reade: Somebody Please Help Me</title>
    <link>http://juliusreade.com/categories/depression/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Depression on Julius Reade: Somebody Please Help Me</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 30 Oct 2016 11:33:26 +1100</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://juliusreade.com/categories/depression/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>Why Intuitive Explanations Are Incredibly Fucking Important</title>
      <link>http://juliusreade.com/2016/10/30/why-intuitive-explanations-are-incredibly-fucking-important/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Oct 2016 11:33:26 +1100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://juliusreade.com/2016/10/30/why-intuitive-explanations-are-incredibly-fucking-important/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;p&gt;So here&amp;rsquo;s the deal. You&amp;rsquo;re not stupid.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Gullible, probably. Delusional, well obviously. I mean, you&amp;rsquo;re on this website so there&amp;rsquo;s clearly something very wrong with you.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;However as long as you have the ability to learn you cannot possibly be stupid. It is what makes you more powerful (and in a lot of cases, more irrational) than every other animal on this planet.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This website covers a number of techniques to help you learn a tremendous amount of information in a short amount of time, and an integral part of this strategy is to explain concepts in an intuitive and engaging way.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now let it be known, while intuitive explanations will rock your world, they only play a small part in the overall learning strategy we will be developing.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There are a lot of other things that we must conquer in order to become highly effective study robots (you will learn about becoming a highly-efficient Japanese sex bot at a later, more advanced stage).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;However it is an excellent starting point for those of us new to the whole &amp;ldquo;Julius Reade lifestyle&amp;rdquo; thing I&amp;rsquo;m clearly trying to sell you.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In a nutshell, here&amp;rsquo;s why intuitive explanations are golden:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;effective-explanations&#34;&gt;Effective Explanations&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Effective explanations are comparable to compelling narratives. They are logical stories which provide us with obvious hints and cues to help us understand any situation.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;These wonderful narratives are designed to assist us in the process of understanding, which be thought of as a timeline of getting from &amp;ldquo;I have literally no idea WHERE I am!&amp;rdquo; to the &amp;ldquo;ah-ha!&amp;rdquo; moment of intuitive and comfortable understanding.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In essence explanations are those vital tools which help us get to our &amp;ldquo;ah-ha!&amp;rdquo; moment of self-realisation, as we now become keenly aware that we&amp;rsquo;re actually trapped in a dungeon in a very SAW-like situation.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Of course, not all explanations are made equal.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;terrible-explanations&#34;&gt;Terrible Explanations&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Terrible explanations, as I&amp;rsquo;m sure you&amp;rsquo;re aware, get us absolutely nowhere.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Like an awful film tied together on a shoe-string budget, the plot makes makes no sense, you&amp;rsquo;re about ready to fall asleep and you still have no idea why the entire cast has been replaced by a series of talking traffic cones.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In fact, terrible explanations can even assist us to misunderstand our situation, bringing on a whole new world of pain to our lives.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Yet what makes terrible explanations so insidious is that they can seem completely rational, while actually being completely wrong and contrary to the actual situation.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Afterall, while humans would like to consider themselve rational creatures,  our collective actions obviously speak in the opposite direction.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Deciphering between good and bad explanations is a seperate skill you will learn to decipher at another time, which becomes crucially important when selecting study material.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For the time being, it can simply help to keep your mind open and not too invested in one set belief or way of thinking.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;!--
Insert article / Write about how to find good study materials.
--&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;average-explanations&#34;&gt;Average Explanations&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Average explanations are no better than terrible explanations.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Like average films, they’re entirely forgettable. They take us 50% of the way there, if we’re lucky, though are generally so bland we&amp;rsquo;ve forgotten what we&amp;rsquo;ve watched by the next day.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Not to mention, this also leaves us with the other 50% of the situation to try and figure out for ourselves, which if you&amp;rsquo;re depressed and stuck in a rut of emotional issues, becomes naturally impossible.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;No. For an explanation to be effective, we need to be taken 90% to 95% of the way there, or as close as possible to full understanding as can be achieved.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Because let’s face it: When you’re depressed and are barely functioning, to expect someone to spend even 10% of their effort to try and help themselves is absurd.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is where intuitive explanations fit in.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Intuitive explanations are like timeless movies. They are beautiful and timeless and can provide us with a convincing narrative to help us better understand who we are.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Intuitive explanations are designed to take us 90% of the way there.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;They are designed to be so easy and obvious, that absolutely anyone can internalise them and come to a level of functional understanding.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If they don&amp;rsquo;t, then it&amp;rsquo;s not your fault. The explanation simply wasn&amp;rsquo;t intuitive enough, which means concepts need to be further broken down so it becomes truly obvious.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Of course, there is a natural limit to these things and intuitive explanations can only take you so far.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Even though intuitive explanations can take you 90%, perhaps even 99% of the way there, you still need to find the effort to do the rest.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is often easier said than done and like anything in life, there are no guarantees, only statistical probabilities.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Never-the-less, this article details an effective and simple process for you to reach that « ah-ha » moment in your mind, or at the very least get you 90% of the way there for when you&amp;rsquo;re ready.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I suppose the insurmountable takeaway from all this is that if you’re struggling with anything in life, it’s most likely because you lack an intuitive understanding of the situation.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Only with intuition can we easily grasp the things which at first seem impossible: Like our depression, for example.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There are a few key reasons why they are important. To name a few, they allow us to dramatically lower the barrier of entry to learning, as well as lower the amount of energy and concentration required to learn.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is critical if we are to take advantage of those moments where we&amp;rsquo;re too tired to do anything rigorous, but still have the energy to absorb information.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One of the primary reasons is that they help us learn at our energy&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>