<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Somebody Please Help Me</title>
    <link>https://juliusreade.com/tags/update/index.xml</link>
    <description>Recent content on Somebody Please Help Me</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>This work is licensed under a Creative Commons Attribution-ShareAlike 4.0 International License.</copyright>
    <atom:link href="https://juliusreade.com/tags/update/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>Non-Postal</title>
      <link>https://juliusreade.com/2017/03/16/non-postal/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Mar 2017 03:23:16 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://juliusreade.com/2017/03/16/non-postal/</guid>
      <description>&lt;!--
Non-Postal

--&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I haven&amp;rsquo;t been posting lately.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And it&amp;rsquo;s entirely your fault.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Naturally I&amp;rsquo;m going to blame you and absolutely anything or anyone else but myself, because of the kind of blight that seeps from your personality like a derelict, sunken ship.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So please allow me to try and paint that glorious picture, that honed nautical possession of fluctuating visual image, which I&amp;rsquo;m sure you&amp;rsquo;ll prize more than the explicitly gorgeous Mona Lisa.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Firstly, I moved house.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Which means I&amp;rsquo;ve been packing shit, boxing shit, arranging dodgy deals with even dodgier people (real estate agents) and let me tell you, it&amp;rsquo;s been an absolute nightmare.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Repeat. An absolute nightmare.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A nightmare I&amp;rsquo;m still dealing with, because the show must go on.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The amount of time I&amp;rsquo;ve spent cleaning, gardening and wasting away on this property defies excess.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;ve had to take time off work. I&amp;rsquo;ve had to argue with the most incompetent house-cleaners. I&amp;rsquo;ve had to wrestle my house-mate into getting anything done.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Please kill me. I honestly dare you.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Anyway, that&amp;rsquo;s all sorted now.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;lol jks, because today I got news that the back and front yard hasn&amp;rsquo;t been ravaged to a high-enough standard yet, which according to their demands, is going to require yet another full day&amp;rsquo;s work.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But that&amp;rsquo;s hardly the issue.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The issue is that they&amp;rsquo;ve literally provided us with one day to prepare, without warning, in lieu of this thing called &amp;ldquo;full-time work&amp;rdquo; otherwise risk losing hundreds of dollars in bond money for the lonely cause of corrupt capitalism.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Not that it actually matters, because a skip is going to cost $250 minimum and yes, I&amp;rsquo;m not very happy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But wait!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There&amp;rsquo;s more!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I have also been horribly sick.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;Under the guise of a nasty fever, I laid there with pride, potentially unremise to the world around me.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The bastard chewed through me like a dead dog.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The worst part is that I contracted the fever on the very morning of the big move out, which following days of strenuous lifting and moving, wasn&amp;rsquo;t very fun.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Not to mention all the additional work getting the house ready for inspection, my actual paid work duties, and it&amp;rsquo;s literally left me with no time to rest.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Three fucking truck loads of house.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In one day.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Listen, I&amp;rsquo;m a fit guy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I lift weights three times a week. I don&amp;rsquo;t eat junk. At the very least I look good.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So I would describe myself as being somewhat capable of pulling my weight.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Let me tell you, my body was in tears by the end of it, and continued to cry for the next week or so.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I could barely walk.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My arms turned to jelly.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Then of course, there&amp;rsquo;s the unpacking, and moving, and general process of finialising everything.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Bleh.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Bleh.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Yo?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Ummmm, I may have also &amp;lsquo;damaged&amp;rsquo; my hands over-typing on my laptop, to the point where I struggle to type without significant paid.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Which meant I had (and continue to have) a difficult time typing anything.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Ideally I wouldn&amp;rsquo;t be typing at all, and allow my hands to fully recover, however I estimate that would take around one month of inactivity, which is highly impractical given my work is fully dependent on using a computer.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Regardless, it&amp;rsquo;s an article I&amp;rsquo;ll attend to at some point.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Oh, and I also relapsed.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One and a half months. I did mighty well and I&amp;rsquo;m on-track now, but when you&amp;rsquo;re sick, bored and alone - why the hell not.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So that&amp;rsquo;s why I haven&amp;rsquo;t been posting lately.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And that&amp;rsquo;s why you should marry me.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>