<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>mental illness on </title>
    <link>https://juliusreade.com/categories/mental-illness/</link>
    <description>Recent content in mental illness on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>This work is licensed under a Creative Commons Attribution-ShareAlike 4.0 International License.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 30 Apr 2017 11:33:26 +1100</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://juliusreade.com/categories/mental-illness/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>My Incredibly Unhealthy Obsession With Success</title>
      <link>https://juliusreade.com/2017/04/30/my-incredibly-unhealthy-obsession-with-success/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Apr 2017 11:33:26 +1100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://juliusreade.com/2017/04/30/my-incredibly-unhealthy-obsession-with-success/</guid>
      <description>I feel as if my drive for success has something to do with my mental illness.
Not necessarily in an inherently bad way (nothing is inherently bad, nor good), but that my obsession is driven by my inadequacies and insecurities.
&amp;hellip;rather than a kind of purity or kindness that perhaps only exists in the land of fairtales.
Part of me feels as if I&amp;rsquo;ve been so traumatised as to be violently pushed towards a direction of success, rather than out of free-will.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Self-Awareness: The Two-Step Tango</title>
      <link>https://juliusreade.com/2017/04/16/self-awareness-the-two-step-tango/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Apr 2017 11:33:26 +1100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://juliusreade.com/2017/04/16/self-awareness-the-two-step-tango/</guid>
      <description>Self-awareness is hard.
It&amp;rsquo;s like a two-headed medusa that knows all your password combinations and spits fire at you, sort of like an ex.
Okay.
Clearly that&amp;rsquo;s a poor comparison, but as you can tell it&amp;rsquo;s something that continues to frustrate me.
Self-awareness is hard because it takes a lot of patience and experience to make work, and even then it&amp;rsquo;s not guaranteed to protect you from your own weaknesses.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Success Is A Verifiable System</title>
      <link>https://juliusreade.com/2017/03/31/success-is-a-verifiable-system/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Mar 2017 07:23:26 +1800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://juliusreade.com/2017/03/31/success-is-a-verifiable-system/</guid>
      <description>Maybe you&amp;rsquo;re a struggle sport.
An undefined blob of human misery, awaiting death in a slurry of shame and complete unanticipation.
Maybe you feel unable to help yourself become successful, either due to lack of knowledge or ability to strive.
That&amp;rsquo;s right.
Welcome to the human experience.
With your host, the shitty human experience co-ordinator.
Perhaps it&amp;rsquo;s because you feel fearful or possibly shameful of the potential outcome, producing anxiety via your own self-perception.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Non-Postal</title>
      <link>https://juliusreade.com/2017/03/16/non-postal/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Mar 2017 03:23:16 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://juliusreade.com/2017/03/16/non-postal/</guid>
      <description>I haven&amp;rsquo;t been posting lately.
And it&amp;rsquo;s entirely your fault.
Naturally I&amp;rsquo;m going to blame you and absolutely anything or anyone else but myself, because of the kind of blight that seeps from your personality like a derelict, sunken ship.
So please allow me to try and paint that glorious picture, that honed nautical possession of fluctuating visual image, which I&amp;rsquo;m sure you&amp;rsquo;ll prize more than the explicitly gorgeous Mona Lisa.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What It Means To Be An Effective Adult</title>
      <link>https://juliusreade.com/2017/02/19/what-it-means-to-be-an-effective-adult/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Feb 2017 03:23:16 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://juliusreade.com/2017/02/19/what-it-means-to-be-an-effective-adult/</guid>
      <description>Millenials like myself are retarded.
We have all these false expectations of what life should be, and in believing so strongly in the advice that has been thrown at us, have failed miserably to cope with the harsh reality of&amp;hellip;
&amp;hellip;not becoming the next big thing on YouTube.
Yep. That&amp;rsquo;s me.
Despite being &amp;lsquo;adults&amp;rsquo; many of us fear commitment, rely too heavily on our parents for financial support, and fail to kickstart our careers in any meaningful way.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>An Intuitive And Simple Guide To Understanding Your Depression</title>
      <link>https://juliusreade.com/2017/02/08/an-intuitive-and-simple-guide-to-understanding-your-depression/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Feb 2017 11:33:26 +1100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://juliusreade.com/2017/02/08/an-intuitive-and-simple-guide-to-understanding-your-depression/</guid>
      <description>The aim of this article is to help you come to terms with your depression.
Ummmm, say what?
Don’t fret, you lucky puck.
I promise it won&amp;rsquo;t involve intense emotional gouging, followed by hours of soul-destroying questioning of your precious most-inner thoughts.
Except that it probably will, so stay tuned.
As you can imagine, depression is a heavy topic with a lot of thorny edges poking at the sides.
Which is why this article won&amp;rsquo;t focus on a number of topics that are vital to understanding depression.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why Young Men Resort To Pick Up</title>
      <link>https://juliusreade.com/2017/01/22/why-young-men-resort-to-pick-up/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Jan 2017 04:23:26 +2020</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://juliusreade.com/2017/01/22/why-young-men-resort-to-pick-up/</guid>
      <description>Firstly, I&amp;rsquo;m quite impartial to pick up.
Despite the fact that pick up is willingly demonised by society, it is also a process that is widely expected of men.
Which traditionally works well&amp;hellip; except for men who are mentally retarded, socially inept or come from broken homes.
You know, like myself.
Happen to lose several limbs in a horrible, though defiantly necessary war?
Forget about it.
Regardless, it&amp;rsquo;s this dynamic that leads to the wide range of sexual activity here on earth, from the consensual to the prolonged jail sentence of your local pedophile.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Have You An Effective Communication With You And Me</title>
      <link>https://juliusreade.com/2017/01/08/have-you-an-effective-communication-with-you-and-me/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Jan 2017 21:39:46 +1600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://juliusreade.com/2017/01/08/have-you-an-effective-communication-with-you-and-me/</guid>
      <description>Let&amp;rsquo;s talk communication.
You know, that one thing many of us fail at miserably.
&amp;ldquo;Great forehead bro, cause it makes me wanna cream like fat Tuesday&amp;rdquo;.
If it&amp;rsquo;s one thing I&amp;rsquo;ve learnt it&amp;rsquo;s that all our traumatic experiences and toxic relationships in life can be attributed to this thing called &amp;lsquo;communcation&amp;rsquo;.
&amp;hellip;or precisely, lack thereof.
When we lack communication between people, we create a number of false assumptions and expectations, that crush us when we realise they&amp;rsquo;re not who we think they are.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Please Don&#39;t Tell Me You&#39;re Sorry</title>
      <link>https://juliusreade.com/2016/12/25/please-dont-tell-me-youre-sorry/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Dec 2016 16:12:30 +1534</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://juliusreade.com/2016/12/25/please-dont-tell-me-youre-sorry/</guid>
      <description>Today we&amp;rsquo;re going to try something new.
Sparkling new.
And for some people this is going to be difficult.
Partly due to the disconnect of reading an article over the internet, as one of the many billions of thoughtless &amp;ldquo;see-things&amp;rdquo; you will probably wade through today.
Apologies in advance for not being physically available in the room with you.
Though not all hope is lost.
What this article CAN probably do for you, is make you that tiny bit more aware of how seemingly useless you are.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Smart People Don&#39;t Think. They Plan Ahead</title>
      <link>https://juliusreade.com/2016/12/11/smart-people-dont-think.-they-plan-ahead/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Dec 2016 16:12:30 +1534</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://juliusreade.com/2016/12/11/smart-people-dont-think.-they-plan-ahead/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;ve managed to develop a lot of dumb habits over the years.
Stalking. Self-harm. Self-obsession. Addiction. Irrational idealisation.
The kinds of habits developed by unadjusted people, because we&amp;rsquo;re stupid and don&amp;rsquo;t seem to know any better.
Ultimately, the cycle itself is fairly basic:
The dumb habit is developed, we assume everything is horrible, and we deny all responsibility and control over the situation.
We fuck up and crave some more, craving and craving until the cows come home.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why Obtaining A Full-time Job Should Be Your Number One Priority</title>
      <link>https://juliusreade.com/2016/11/27/why-obtaining-a-full-time-job-should-be-your-number-one-priority/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Nov 2016 14:53:55 +1100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://juliusreade.com/2016/11/27/why-obtaining-a-full-time-job-should-be-your-number-one-priority/</guid>
      <description>Committing towards a full-time job is one of the most fundamental things you can do in life to secure your future success.
Not because of the money or the tireless hours spent making someone else rich.
Those things are inconsequential to the true benefits of working full-time. Benefits which are incredibly difficult to replicate in other systems.
Blah. Blah. Blah.
Though perhaps you already know this.
Perhaps you&amp;rsquo;ve already experienced first-hand the crushing resilience that full-time work forces upon you.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What It Means To Be A Porn Addict</title>
      <link>https://juliusreade.com/2016/11/13/what-it-means-to-be-a-porn-addict/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Nov 2016 11:33:26 +1100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://juliusreade.com/2016/11/13/what-it-means-to-be-a-porn-addict/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m a pornography addict and quite frankly, it sucks.
I decided to write this article in order to provide some closure into what happens in my mind when I go full addict.
Because even though it&amp;rsquo;s an issue most men face and widely accept, I personally believe it&amp;rsquo;s not okay.
So rather than brush it over, I&amp;rsquo;m choosing to address it for the betterment of myself and society.
As always, addiction is an incredibly intimate and personal experience that touches us all in different ways.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Intuitive Explanations Make You Dizzyingly Smart</title>
      <link>https://juliusreade.com/2016/10/30/intuitive-explanations-make-you-dizzyingly-smart/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Oct 2016 11:33:26 +1100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://juliusreade.com/2016/10/30/intuitive-explanations-make-you-dizzyingly-smart/</guid>
      <description>You&amp;rsquo;re not stupid.
Gullible, probably. Delusional? Well, obviously.
I mean you&amp;rsquo;re on this website designed for misfit derelicts, which clearly indicates that there&amp;rsquo;s something very wrong with you.
Yet I don&amp;rsquo;t think you&amp;rsquo;re stupid.
Because as long as you have the ability to learn, you cannot possibly be stupid.
Your ability to learn is what makes you more powerful (and in a lot of cases, more irrational) than any other animal on this planet.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>