<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>adelaidesucks on </title>
    <link>https://juliusreade.com/tags/adelaidesucks/</link>
    <description>Recent content in adelaidesucks on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>This work is licensed under a Creative Commons Attribution-ShareAlike 4.0 International License.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 20 Nov 2007 13:10:30 +0934</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://juliusreade.com/tags/adelaidesucks/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>The child who watched anime…………</title>
      <link>https://juliusreade.com/adelaidesucks/the-child-who-watched-anime/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Nov 2007 13:10:30 +0934</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://juliusreade.com/adelaidesucks/the-child-who-watched-anime/</guid>
      <description>Something i wrote during music:
“Damn it” I shouted. Although it was a happy moment, I stared in disgust. “What the hell……….go clean yourself up”. Alex looked down and cried but I showed no signs of sympathy. “Make sure you wash around your pants as well”. He knew that he was in trouble.
As Alex walked out of the room, cheers of laughter and triumph were heard. Alex knew clearly that he was unwanted, in a gay sort of way.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why the hell is it so hot? (And this time it isn&#39;t me)</title>
      <link>https://juliusreade.com/adelaidesucks/why-the-hell-is-it-so-hot-and-this-time-it-isnt-me/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Nov 2007 18:23:30 +0934</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://juliusreade.com/adelaidesucks/why-the-hell-is-it-so-hot-and-this-time-it-isnt-me/</guid>
      <description>As i look outside my front porch, i see people covered in flames; melted tar stuck to there faces screaming: &amp;ldquo;Help!!!! Help!!!! I&amp;rsquo;m on fire&amp;rdquo;, and no matter how many times i see it happen, i still break into laughter, but why is it so damn hot outside? Or maybe a better question to ask: Why do i continue to wear long pants and shirts with sleeves? Well as we all know (from my past experiences with the media), i have a too large a profile, which means that ANY revealed part of my body would cause much tension between the paparazzi whether to put it on page 1 or 7.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Save as a draft</title>
      <link>https://juliusreade.com/adelaidesucks/save-as-a-draft/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Nov 2007 10:18:30 +0934</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://juliusreade.com/adelaidesucks/save-as-a-draft/</guid>
      <description>As a kind and loving person, you may be aware that there is also another side to me. Whether it may be my recent claims that the &amp;ldquo;Pham organization&amp;rdquo; are evil, or the fact that i am hot, we must now realize that there are other role models in life that can deliver far more than what i can offer. Further examples prove that not only am i unworthy, but also a person that hates reading and socializing with girls.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Influence of Jane</title>
      <link>https://juliusreade.com/adelaidesucks/influence-of-jane/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Nov 2007 11:42:30 +0934</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://juliusreade.com/adelaidesucks/influence-of-jane/</guid>
      <description>Ignorant, racist, unfair. Just some of the words to describe a particular people, or also known as &amp;ldquo;The People of Pham&amp;rdquo;. Through out the years, people have struggled, but why? Up until now, we have discovered the real culprit and his minions and the fact that they have been among us the whole time.
Many theories suggested that global warming was to blame, but HARD EVIDENCE PROVES that it was actually one of the many evil leaders in the &amp;ldquo;Pham&amp;rdquo; organization.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Role model for 2007.</title>
      <link>https://juliusreade.com/adelaidesucks/role-model-for-2007./</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Nov 2007 21:52:30 +0934</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://juliusreade.com/adelaidesucks/role-model-for-2007./</guid>
      <description>Despite the fact that this blog most definitely not keeping you informed with issues that matter, i think as a people we can say i have extraordinary talent from within. But as much as i can brag about myself, i also have the ability to work miracles, that even make the worthy cry. Which brings me to my unrelated issue&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;.my upcoming top ?? list which will contain the essentials components to functional music.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>One Blog. Two Outcomes.</title>
      <link>https://juliusreade.com/adelaidesucks/one-blog.-two-outcomes./</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Nov 2007 21:52:30 +0934</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://juliusreade.com/adelaidesucks/one-blog.-two-outcomes./</guid>
      <description>May i please say (Although i have all right to say this that) there can be no equal outcome with the exsistence of this blog. Thus there are two main outcomes that either you or I must suffer. These are:
 You come to my blog and you add on to the total number of visitors to this site. This results in me being happy and you having to suffer the &amp;ldquo;bad comedy&amp;rdquo; of my articles.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Non-Update 3#</title>
      <link>https://juliusreade.com/adelaidesucks/non-update-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Nov 2007 21:11:30 +0934</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://juliusreade.com/adelaidesucks/non-update-3/</guid>
      <description>Lol&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;..If you look at my stats the number of visitors have gone down by one each day (sorta). Also I know that i have so called &amp;ldquo;viewers&amp;rdquo; but i cant be certain, (According to the stat counter). If you are one please place i comment in the comment thing
Thx
Ps: i have AT LEAST one. (Probaly Bryan)
 Nice try Alan, you have no evidence&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My Adventures as a level one mage..........</title>
      <link>https://juliusreade.com/adelaidesucks/my-adventures-as-a-level-one-mage........../</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Nov 2007 14:25:30 +0934</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://juliusreade.com/adelaidesucks/my-adventures-as-a-level-one-mage........../</guid>
      <description>Under my Maplestory account (Until i realised it was possibly the worlds worst game), i adventured through the land of MapleStory, (or what ever it was called) and began the legacy which was me. As i entered the portal to the new land, i was confronted with what many would call a &amp;ldquo;blue snail&amp;rdquo;, which looks easy enough to kill. Which is when i came to my common senses&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;..
Up until this point i pity the fools who play that game, as it is truly a boring and unpleasant experience.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Another one of my ****ing guides..............</title>
      <link>https://juliusreade.com/adelaidesucks/another-one-of-my-ing-guides............../</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Nov 2007 09:44:30 +0934</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://juliusreade.com/adelaidesucks/another-one-of-my-ing-guides............../</guid>
      <description>This week (or at least i think so), i will be guiding many unguided Australian&amp;rsquo;s (people) that have been struggling with exams and etc. However, you&amp;rsquo;re probably asking, why the **** are you telling me after my exams? Well even miracle workers, such as myself can&amp;rsquo;t answer that question, which is why we move on to the first step.
Cheat. Although i don&amp;rsquo;t encourage cheating, i do &amp;ldquo;ADVISE&amp;rdquo; that you TRY it out *wink* **wink**.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Non Update #2</title>
      <link>https://juliusreade.com/adelaidesucks/non-update-#2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Nov 2007 19:32:30 +0934</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://juliusreade.com/adelaidesucks/non-update-#2/</guid>
      <description>But that doesn&amp;rsquo;t matter because no body reads this shit anyway :)&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;..</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Non-Update</title>
      <link>https://juliusreade.com/adelaidesucks/non-update/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Nov 2007 13:52:30 +0934</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://juliusreade.com/adelaidesucks/non-update/</guid>
      <description>Haven&amp;rsquo;t posted/updated lately because of exams. And can&amp;rsquo;t until exams r over :)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I hate anime.............. [Part 2]</title>
      <link>https://juliusreade.com/adelaidesucks/i-hate-anime..............-part-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Nov 2007 15:44:30 +0934</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://juliusreade.com/adelaidesucks/i-hate-anime..............-part-2/</guid>
      <description>Today we will be looking at ways to suppress the anime movement and anime enthusiasts in general. For help i asked Doctor George Flanagan and he told me that there are 3 main steps. Quote: &amp;ldquo;Remember Julius, there are three main steps&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;&amp;quot;, too bad i forgot what he said afterwards which is why i Made up my own: Refuse, Convince, Tazer.
The First step is to Refuse any of the persons requests, e.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I hate anime..............</title>
      <link>https://juliusreade.com/adelaidesucks/i-hate-anime............../</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Nov 2007 02:54:30 +0934</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://juliusreade.com/adelaidesucks/i-hate-anime............../</guid>
      <description>Imagine a concept worse than aids. Worse than the possibility of death and boredom in a cartoon&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;..
Or you could just watch anime?
Short for &amp;ldquo;I am gay&amp;rdquo; in Japanese, anime has inspired many to become freaks of nature, often looking for help in secluded areas. But why do people enjoy watching it? Are people becoming so desperate? Or am i just making this up?
I asked Psychologist Tim Regan, and he told me some shocking figures.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Top 177 Song List</title>
      <link>https://juliusreade.com/adelaidesucks/top-177-song-list/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Oct 2007 18:30:30 +0934</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://juliusreade.com/adelaidesucks/top-177-song-list/</guid>
      <description>Updated Randomly&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;
I am Damn sick of people who say they listen to good music&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;..
&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;..Which is why i have created this blog to show the losers in society about MUSIC. But here are some question first:
-Do you want to be gay at school (or the workplace)?
-I am a complete retard?
-I have no friends and want to remain this way?
-I am still breast fed by my dad?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Julius how to guide.............</title>
      <link>https://juliusreade.com/adelaidesucks/julius-how-to-guide............./</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Oct 2007 14:57:30 +0934</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://juliusreade.com/adelaidesucks/julius-how-to-guide............./</guid>
      <description>Now as we all know, my personal fan base in South Korea has been requesting for a guide on &amp;ldquo;How to get laid&amp;rdquo; which is why i prepared a little something earlier on&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;.
 There are many reasons why people don&amp;rsquo;t get laid, but here are the reasons why you should:
 It forces you to read this guide, which means absolutely nothing. Saves you money each Friday night. Provides a near impossible challenge, from reading this guide.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Top 252 song List (Updated)</title>
      <link>https://juliusreade.com/adelaidesucks/top-252-song-list-updated/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Oct 2007 12:08:30 +0934</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://juliusreade.com/adelaidesucks/top-252-song-list-updated/</guid>
      <description>The list had Been updated, with songs and fixed up. Enjoy.
I also strongly encourage that you try and download MOST OF these songs legally. (Wink Wink, Nudge Nudge). But then again, my friend was telling me about A little program called Limewire&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;
Overall, if you do download them (which would take a long time) you should like a majority of the songs (depending on whether you are a music freak like me, or a loser in society&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Suggested Websites</title>
      <link>https://juliusreade.com/adelaidesucks/suggested-websites/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Oct 2007 11:18:30 +0934</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://juliusreade.com/adelaidesucks/suggested-websites/</guid>
      <description>Ummmmm also, you might need these&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;.. http://gctracker.mine.nu:800/index.php - Gamecube isos ( Torrent) www.fat-pie.com - The only reason why i can&amp;rsquo;t get to sleep&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;. www.fat-pie.com/jerryjackson.htm - U must not forget this&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip; http://www.deeko.com/store.asp - The only place to buy games online&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;..
 http://melbournehighschool.editboard.com/index.htm - Forum, can&amp;rsquo;t remember what happened to it though&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;.oh wait i got suspended? http://mhsforums.17.forumer.com/ - Actual working one, surprised though&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;.. http://downloads.khinsider.com/ - For the nerds&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;.video game nerds&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;.. http://seehere.blogspot.com/ - A much better Blog&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>