<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title></title>
    <link>https://juliusreade.com/tags/addiction/index.xml</link>
    <description>Recent content on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>This work is licensed under a Creative Commons Attribution-ShareAlike 4.0 International License.</copyright>
    <atom:link href="https://juliusreade.com/tags/addiction/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>What It Means To Be A Porn Addict</title>
      <link>https://juliusreade.com/2016/11/13/what-it-means-to-be-a-porn-addict/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Nov 2016 11:33:26 +1100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://juliusreade.com/2016/11/13/what-it-means-to-be-a-porn-addict/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;m a pornography addict and quite frankly, it sucks.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What this essentially means is that I don&amp;rsquo;t have full control over my pornography habit.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I mean, I&amp;rsquo;ve gotten pretty far and can usually abstain for months at a time, however it always seems to catch up with me to some capacity or another.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Which is pretty good, considering I don&amp;rsquo;t really have any other vices.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I decided to write this article in order to provide some closure into what happens in my mind when I go full addict.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Because even though it&amp;rsquo;s an issue most men face and widely accept, I personally believe it&amp;rsquo;s not okay.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So rather than brush it over, I&amp;rsquo;m choosing to address it for the betterment of myself and society.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As always, addiction is an incredibly intimate and personal experience that touches us all in different ways.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Some addictions are minor.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;They are meaningless preambles driven by chemical reactions and perverted curiosity.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Foolish choices that drive the dopamine in our minds at a meander&amp;rsquo;s stumble, as part of the routine congo line of lust and gluttony we all carry without care.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;At best they are vague inconveniences, tarnishing our image with a feint smudge of human indecency - a blemish that is soon forgotten, if not unnoticed.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;These are the kinds of addictions that fail to keep us up at night.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;On the other end of the spectrum however, are addictions driven by our beliefs:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;By the belief we must feel loved by a certain individual.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;By the belief that our self-worth is unattainable.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;By the belief self-harm serves a higher purpose, despite our best intentions to logically resist and conquer.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;These are the kinds of addictions that point a gun to our heads, smothering mother nature and her faculty with smaug indecency, breaking us down into helpless incapable animals with no sense of life or direction.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In my own particular case, my relationship with pornography is the kind of addiction that resides in the depths of my beliefs.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Beliefs perpetuated by an insidious insecurity that eats away at me, swiftly evading my ability to think or comprehend.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Consume and squander. The motions feel no pain.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I am addict.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;While I don&amp;rsquo;t fully understand my pornography addiction, I know enough about it to be able to explain the narrative that takes place in my mind when I turn addict, and as a result, can largely control the outcome.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Though certainly without consistency.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I will relapse and continue to relapse, time and time again, if not due to the flawed simplicity of human nature.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Though arguably I&amp;rsquo;ve become used to it - an issue which I must address.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;where-we-all-began&#34;&gt;Where We All Began&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://juliusreade.com/img/blog/02-01.png&#34; alt=&#34;The Story Of How My Pornography Addiction Began&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Like most male teenagers growing up, I would masturbate to pornography.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It was equivalent to drinking soft-drink or playing a few rounds of Modern Warfare with the boys.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;They did it. I did it. Everyone else I knew did it. It was considered a normal part of the teenage experience.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;hellip;and then you grow up.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To &amp;ldquo;grow up&amp;rdquo; is a very personal thing, however for me it was this sudden urge to no longer accept the self-perceived limitations of being a child.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To take responsibility of my own life, rather than flow with the circumstances surrounding it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I believe this so-called &amp;ldquo;growing up&amp;rdquo; is a crucial period in a man&amp;rsquo;s life where one ultimately aims to discover what it means to be male.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A period of self-definition and self-discovery, of becoming your own role model and redefining who you are.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Though perhaps it was just me.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I mean, I didn&amp;rsquo;t exactly grow up with a central, functional father figure, so perhaps it was an itch I&amp;rsquo;d always wanted to target within myself.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Regardless, the urge was strong.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I began improving my health and fitness.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I developed an interest in knowledge, philosophy and self-help literature. I began pursuing my dreams and ambitions, as if nothing could stop me.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One by one, I redefined my own morality and shed the self-percieved notions of my personality holding me down.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I became smarter, stronger and more resilient, and it is a process that continues till this day.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Yet no matter how hard I&amp;rsquo;ve tried, I&amp;rsquo;ve never managed to fully crack my pornography addiction.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I mean, I&amp;rsquo;ve been able to refrain from it for months at a time and it&amp;rsquo;s not an issue after I abstain for a week or so, however the addiction has always remained a reoccurring trend: a brutal curiosity I cannot quite kick.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In this sense, I&amp;rsquo;ve always viewed pornography as the last frontier in my quest to become a better person, and it is a symbolism that holds strong in my mind.&lt;br /&gt;
Part of the reason for this addiction is due to the extreme confidence issues I developed growing up, which unfortunately persisted into my early 20s&amp;rsquo;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I simply felt like I wasn&amp;rsquo;t good enough to attract women.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In addition, the brief experiences I&amp;rsquo;d had with women had left a pretty horrible impression on what I thought relationships were, and so I viewed pornography as the only real alternative.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I was young and that&amp;rsquo;s just how it was.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;That&amp;rsquo;s just how I was.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;i-am-addict&#34;&gt;I Am Addict&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://juliusreade.com/img/blog/02-02.png&#34; alt=&#34;I Am Addict&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As I&amp;rsquo;m sure you&amp;rsquo;re probably aware, the act of orgasming is a naturally addictive behaviour.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It is a dopamine bunny of &amp;ldquo;Fuck Yeah!&amp;rdquo; linked to man&amp;rsquo;s most primal desire: To impregnate the world in a slurry of cum and unfortunate teenage mothers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Throw in the hyper-reality and extreme projection of plastic surgery, and masturbating to pornography genuinely feels as if you&amp;rsquo;re on top of the world, having sex with the world&amp;rsquo;s most exclusive women.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You see, men are largely visual creatures, especially when it comes to attraction.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;That&amp;rsquo;s how they get you.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In fact, it&amp;rsquo;s amazing how the human brain can convincingly trick itself into thinking it&amp;rsquo;s fucking an actual woman through a bunch of two-dimensional visual cues on my computer screen.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As for how pornography contributes towards this destructive dynamic, the narrative of hyper-reality goes a little something like this, though I&amp;rsquo;m sure it&amp;rsquo;s better explained elsewhere:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For thousands if not millions of years up until recently, before the advent of computers and wide-spread electronics, communication and mobility amongst humans was limited.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Chances are that you lived in the same area, with the same set of neighbours, with the same culmination of knowledge and culture, for your entire bloody life.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You didn&amp;rsquo;t have much exposure to other cultures or communities, because it simply wasn&amp;rsquo;t economical.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Well, at least for a majority of the population working on a farm or in the town centre.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As a result you lived in your own little world, mutual from the excess grandeurs of life. It was a beautiful equilibrium that agreed with the natural mechanisms of your brain.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In this scenario, statistically speaking, everything in your world would have existed in a perfect bell-curve distribution relative to the surrounding population.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As per the bell-curve distribution, a majority of the people in your world would have been of average attractiveness.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;On the outliers of this bell-curve were those who were incredibly attractive, as well as those who were beaten to death with the ugly stick.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Not that it affected your perception of the world, because your mind was never particularly overwhelmed by hoards of ugly or attractive people.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In fact, you would only see them very occassionally, much like in real life.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It was a stable distribution which kept your dopamine and expectations in check.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It was &amp;ldquo;fair&amp;rdquo; if you could ever call it that.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Of course, we now live in the 21st century where this stable distribution is no longer.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With television and the internet, we now have enough wires and cables to make even your most absurd sensory desires into a digital reality.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In the process significantly fucking with the stable bell-curve distribution our minds had largely become adjusted to over the past few million years.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Leaving us with the cluster fuck that is pornography addiction and god-knows what else. (Video game addiction, anyone?)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With the internet well and alive, we can now view incredibly attractive women, completely naked at their most intimate, 24 hours a day, 7 days a week, whenever we desire.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Not to mention, completely free of charge.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I mean, fuck it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Of course I&amp;rsquo;m going to become a porn addict. You&amp;rsquo;d have to be a freak not to, and that&amp;rsquo;s often how people like myself viewed other guys who didn&amp;rsquo;t watch pornography:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Lunatics.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Furthermore, it&amp;rsquo;s not just the increasing accessibility and quality of pornography which seems to be growing in leaps and bounds.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The way pornography is distributed over the internet is another integral part of what sucks you into the addictive matrix, spitting you out like a deformed slobber of inconsequential im-immaterial.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You see, pornography websites are a lot like wandering through a perpetual casino of perversion and lust, where your every interaction is a sucker-punch injection of pure dopamine to the skull.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;At no point do you not feel compelled to click and explore&amp;hellip; and give your life away.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With thousands upon thousands of pornography categories vying for your attention, amongst the millions of videos currently available to the modern consumer, you break down into a modern slave.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A slave to your own senses.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Because part of the thrill is that you never know what you&amp;rsquo;ll find next and after a while, you notice that you can derive more pleasure from simply browsing through these video looking for that next great video, rather than from watching the porn itself.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Hundreds upon hundreds of videos for hours on end, waiting for that perfect moment.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A perfect moment that doesn&amp;rsquo;t exist.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Because you&amp;rsquo;re an addict.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You&amp;rsquo;re a fucking addict and you don&amp;rsquo;t care.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Even a strong part of you knows it&amp;rsquo;s bullshit, yet it&amp;rsquo;s this beautiful ruse that keeps you going.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A culture designed to cradle you to your deathbed.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;the-dark-and-twisted-side-of-pornography-addiction&#34;&gt;The Dark And Twisted Side of Pornography Addiction&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://juliusreade.com/img/blog/02-03.png&#34; alt=&#34;The Dark And Twisted Side of Pornography Addiction&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Of course, the addiction doesn&amp;rsquo;t stop there.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It fundamentally warps you in ways that discards your humanity and turns you into a monster.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The guilt and degradation you feel eventually leaks into your perception, as it crawls its way into the pornography viewing experience.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You no longer view these women as mere &amp;lsquo;pleasure things&amp;rsquo;. You instead watch them with an intense observation, from the point of view of a performance.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You psyco-analyse them with an evil curiosity. How much is she faking it? Is she on drugs? Does she have emotional issues?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It is a perspective that changes the way you view women, not as actual people, but as mere NPCs.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You soon get off to the fact that it&amp;rsquo;s not real and that these people are not truly enjoying the experience they&amp;rsquo;ve signed up for.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It pleasures you to catch glimpse of their suffering, as you witness their false laughter momentarily falter into an uneasy smile of sadness and regret.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You get off to the hurt they feel inside and you encourage it in your selection of pornography.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Gang-bangs. Electro-shock therapy. Scars left from self-harm.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Their discomfort becomes your pleasure.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I once remember watching a small white girl get gang-banged by a bunch of black men.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You could see that she was incredibly uncomfortable and in pain, all while these men taunted her and made feel like shit in the most worst possible way.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It immediately occurred to me that she was being raped (to the extent that she was doing it for money, but was clearly both mentally and physically distressed).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But as much as it disturbed me, I didn&amp;rsquo;t care.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I was me, pursuing the humble chemicals in my brain, because they were all that mattered in the moments to come.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Me and my emotions, dangling by a thread of irrational bespoke ingenuity.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I believe part of this behaviour comes down to the desensitisation that takes place in the advent of addiction.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When the dopamine no longer functions, you&amp;rsquo;re left with no choice but to attach yourself to a series of more evocative emotions and feelings.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Such as adrenaline.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So you start viewing pornography videos with shock value.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Your tastes turn from pleasure to violence in this quest to feel that you&amp;rsquo;re winning.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Of course, another reason is to bring her conceptually down to your own level.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Because when you become a porn addict, that recognisable, empathetic part of your human disappears.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And you want her to feel that too.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You want her to feel as worthless and dysfunctional as you are.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I suppose this was an extension of the hopelessness I&amp;rsquo;d always felt as a teenager growing up, in particular in regards to my over-bearing asian mother.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In order to cope, I found it helped to naturally give up in my mind and over time, I learnt to appreciate this feeling of hopelessness, guilt and shame as something sensual, rather than unpleasant.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I discovered that if I could keep my happiness and ambitions to a minimum, that perhaps life wouldn&amp;rsquo;t be so bad.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So part me craved that feeling of being controlled and being used and my pornography addiction allow me to experience that helplessness.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I suppose pornography addicts are somewhat somewhat masochistic in that sense.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For part of me craves that dysfunction of being a victim.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And I&amp;rsquo;m sure in some immature way, allows me to feel as if I am in control.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Certainly, I am culprit to this kind of thinking (or romanticisation) and I think part of it comes down to the way in which addiction touches us.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It doesn&amp;rsquo;t just poke, or prod.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It completely ravishes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I genuinely believe humans are somewhat obsessed with their vulnerabilities.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;hellip;exploring that dark place and letting yourself go from responsibility, to explore everything civilisation wants you to repress.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To discover something interesting in the observation of our disconfigured self.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;That moment of disbelief where you wonder if your mind is tricking you into believing that it&amp;rsquo;s really, truly you.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Though perhaps that&amp;rsquo;s just my pornography addiction speaking.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;the-impact-pornography-addiction-has-had-on-my-life&#34;&gt;The Impact Pornography Addiction Has Had On My Life&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://juliusreade.com/img/blog/02-04.png&#34; alt=&#34;The Impact Pornography Addiction Has Had On My Life&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I would argue that the failure of my first two relationships were due to my pornography addiction.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Okay, perhaps that&amp;rsquo;s pushing it - I was awful in a lot of different ways, but I feel that I wouldn&amp;rsquo;t have been so awful if it weren&amp;rsquo;t for the expectations that pornography addiction had set for me.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Certainly if it&amp;rsquo;s one thing I can advise: please don&amp;rsquo;t date a porn addict.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We will ruin your life in the worst possible way and make you feel like cheap dirt. It is something I have been culprit to and all I can say is that I&amp;rsquo;m much better now.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Not that I deserve anyone&amp;rsquo;s trust or sympathy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When you&amp;rsquo;re addicted to pornography you no longer view women as other human beings.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You no longer view them as a collection of their talents and wonderful quirks. Their smiles. Their laughter.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You instead you view them as eye-candy, to be fucked and discarded.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I suppose what makes pornography addiction so difficult is that it has affected my perception of women from an incredibly young age (I believe I started when I was 10 years old).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Not only due to pornography, but also due to the generally horrible treatment I&amp;rsquo;ve received from women.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In addition, I would argue that pornography addiction is a large part of the reason why most men struggle to communicate effectively with women.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We simply can&amp;rsquo;t get over wanting to fuck you enough to actually have a normal conversation.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Whenever I talk to another women it&amp;rsquo;s like my porn brain switches on and I have to somehow fight myself not to think about sex.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I think pornography is in part responsible for the whole pick-up scene: Insecure men wanting to fuck their porn fantasises at any cost.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The absolute worst consequence of my habit however, is the lying and hiding from my partner that comes with being an addict.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I can certainly attest that the feeling of betraying the trust of someone you love most is something that you do not forget.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In a recent episode of relapse, I was watching pornography on my laptop when my girlfriend entered the room, prompting me to minimise the tab and minimise the volume to mute.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Anyway, she thought it would be really cute to take a video of us on my laptop, so she grabbed it off me and turned the volume on.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;She was shocked and left the room.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Don&amp;rsquo;t be that guy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It&amp;rsquo;s devastating being that guy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;how-i-prevent-my-pornography-addiction&#34;&gt;How I Prevent My Pornography Addiction&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://juliusreade.com/img/blog/02-05.png&#34; alt=&#34;How I Prevent My Pornography Addiction&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;While the obvious purpose of this article was to expose how horrible pornography addiction is, it is also important to note that I&amp;rsquo;m very rarely these things anymore.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;That is to say that I can usually refrain from my addiction 90% of the time.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I won&amp;rsquo;t turn this into a guide on how to prevent pornography addiction, however I can happily say that I am not my addiction.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The biggest benefit from abstaining is that I develop this incredible, laser-like focus.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;ll write about the benefits in a different post, in particular discussing the benefits of refraining from orgasm in general - however not today, folks.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I think part of what makes pornography addiction so difficult is that it&amp;rsquo;s not quite on the level of drinking or smoking in terms of health detriment, which makes it seem relatively harmless.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Yet the psychological toll of pornography on your perception of women is arguably much worse.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Not to mention, orgasming five times in a row really drains you.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In essence pornography addiction still allows you to live and function in society without being questioned, as it is neither an expensive, nor obvious habit.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It&amp;rsquo;s impossible to notice a pornography addict, because there&amp;rsquo;s nothing to hide.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It&amp;rsquo;s all hidden away in the depths of your mind.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In terms of recovery, the biggest thing that&amp;rsquo;s helped me overcome my pornography addiction, by far, is being in a stable relationship.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Not only has it taught me about what love with another person should be (as opposed to an interracial orgy with five black men), however my significant other keeps me accountable.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Furthermore, sexual contact with another human being helps desensitise me from pornography.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It like, has the opposite effect to pornography.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A readjusting to reality, so-to-speak.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In terms of being triggered, there are basically two things I need to do in order to keep my pornography addiction in check.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The first and most important measure is to refrain from orgasm, because once I orgasm it&amp;rsquo;s literally game over.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;99% of the time I&amp;rsquo;ll return back to my pornography addiction within a few hours.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Very rarely (basically never) will I just give in my pornography addiction, because the urge simply isn&amp;rsquo;t there when I&amp;rsquo;m stable.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Usually it&amp;rsquo;s by accident through sex (though I&amp;rsquo;m quite good at remaining on edge after years of practice) or because we&amp;rsquo;ve decided to be naughty and give into our desires during.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thankfully we&amp;rsquo;re both highly aware of the consequences through repeated error, and so we usually remain adult enough to refrain from it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The second part is to minimise my exposure to anything too heavy on the sex appeal chart.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This means refraining from watching movies with sex scenes or that have anything to do with sex. Documentaries on pornography and sexuality are a big no-no.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Hell, I can&amp;rsquo;t even watch Modern Family because of the abnormally large breast size of the cast.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In addition, I will relapse when my relationship isn&amp;rsquo;t functioning as I&amp;rsquo;d like it to, which usually happens once a month when we have a big fight.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Come to think of it, a HUGE trigger for me is when I fall sick.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The moment I fall sick, I generally give up on most things, including my ambitions.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I stop eating healthily, I masturbate and I no longer care about anything.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I also generally relapse if my girlfriend is away for a long period of time.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Oh, and sometimes do it because I view it as a challenge, not knowing that&amp;rsquo;s going to be hell. Well, I downplay it in my mind, because I&amp;rsquo;m an idiot.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Put simply, addicts cannot be trusted and I am not to be trusted with my addiction.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I am only to be trusted when I have a process; a set of rules in place to keep me check. Then I&amp;rsquo;m mostly fine.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Personally speaking, complete abstinence from orgasm is the only thing that works for me.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So there you have it. This is who I am.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A broken, masturbating contraption of misery and regret.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;At least according to this article.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;!--



We equate the anxiety and wanting to this wistfully incomprehensible daze of wonderful illusion, akin to a magical dream state of tainted joy. 
, even though addiction is nothing like that. 

Addiction is this horrible, insincere and unpleasant experience beyond a few magnitudes. So how do we get so stupid?


In some ways, it is a culmination of the guilt and shame we feel on a daily basis, perpetuated by a kind of hopelessness that not only ravages, but completely destroys as well. 

It is a mental asphyxiation of self-deficiency and anxiousness, shoved and forced without context. A self-determined condition that etches its message into your every thought, in a subliminal wanting. 


Arguably, I don&#39;t believe that makes it anymore okay doesn&#39;t make it anymore okay. 


Perhaps a good place to start is 

Porn addiction means a lot of different things. 

Largely, it is a process of mandatory desensitization. 



You see, you make small aggreements in your head. When you make enough of them, you 


The only thing that works for me is complete abstinence from orgasm. 

I can still have sex, 

There&#39;s a lot of limitations. I cannot etc. 



It&#39;s like experience some kind of grand reset. 





To me, porn addiction means not being able to orgasm during sex. 

Porn addiction means refraining myself from all forms of sex appeal. 



Arguably, most men I know are addicted to porn.

It&#39;s a widely know, accepted fact, no different to sugar or coffee addiction. It&#39;s unsaid, because it&#39;s assumed. In fact, apparently it&#39;s weird not to watch porn. 

Quite simply, it&#39;s not right.

Though I&#39;m not here to judge and provide a meta-examiniation of the socio-political aspects of porn addiction. Instead, I want to talk about my own personal experience and struggle with pornography.

I suppose it is a topic that is  close to me because it is a habit that has persisted since childhood.

I mean, I&#39;ve tried a lot of different drugs and hell, I&#39;ve even managed to get over a large portion of my mental illness - so I think that&#39;s saying something.

The good news is that I can largely control my addiction if I follow a bunch of strict guidelines, though I will generally relapse to varying degrees once every month or two months. 

It in general means I need to refrain myself from the porn mindset, which makes me want to do horribel things. 

Simply knowing the horrible things I&#39;ve done as a result of pornography addiction is something that is a great source of guilt and shame for me. It makes me feel worthless to know all the harm I have caused in my own, and other people&#39;s lives. 


As time went along however these feelings would evolve into something greater. 

Soon the hopelessness would transpire into guilt and shame, and soon too, would I come to enjoy these emotions. 

Like a tangled vine, it would consume and walk all over me and it grew until I learnt to like it.

The guilt and shame reflected on how I felt in general about myself as this smart, though worthless creature. 

It suited my personality and how I felt, so I didn&#39;t have to question it. It simply was who I was. 



Pornography addiction is a horrible and debilitating condition that rips into your soul, and exposes a kind of vulnerability that consumes you to the point of asphyxiation.

It is an on-going battle that never ends, no matter how confident or determined you think you are. 

And quite frankly, it sucks. 


--&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>