<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title></title>
    <link>https://juliusreade.com/categories/forgiveness/index.xml</link>
    <description>Recent content on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>This work is licensed under a Creative Commons Attribution-ShareAlike 4.0 International License.</copyright>
    <atom:link href="https://juliusreade.com/categories/forgiveness/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>Compassion Is Masturbation Without The Guilt</title>
      <link>https://juliusreade.com/2017/07/23/compassion-is-masturbation-without-the-guilt/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Jul 2017 03:16:22 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://juliusreade.com/2017/07/23/compassion-is-masturbation-without-the-guilt/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;p&gt;Compassion is the process of learning to unconditionally love.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Ideally, to unconditionally love and accept ourselves for who we are.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A process which we often substitute with dopamine and cigarettes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In an attempt to distract ourselves long enough in the slight off-chance happiness may come our way.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Only to feel empty and hollow inside.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And much in the same way, confuse masturbation or eating a slice of cake with the inner workings of a viable coping mechanism.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Welcome to the human experience.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now obviously, this process of learning to love is an important aspect of life.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Yet it&amp;rsquo;s a step most of us completely disregard.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Instead, we opt to chase our fears and insecurities, as well as the dopamine that comes with inhaling our favourite substances.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Certainly, I don&amp;rsquo;t think compassion is particularly hard.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It&amp;rsquo;s something that most of us inherently want to do, provided a healthy environment and supportive peers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Instead, where I believe most of us fail is in here (I&amp;rsquo;m currently pointing to my brain).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We forget to be compassionate.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As in, we literally forget about compassion as a concept.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Most of us are so preoccupied with all the stress and negativity in our lives, that we don&amp;rsquo;t give it a chance to enter our mind.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To grow with it and become it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It&amp;rsquo;s the reason we don&amp;rsquo;t meditate or choose to calm down when our anxiety strikes - it&amp;rsquo;s just not hard-wired into how we think.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The good news is that we&amp;rsquo;re already halfway there.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Humans naturally tend towards compassion, so there&amp;rsquo;s nothing to learn here.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The bad news is that you&amp;rsquo;ll have to learn to consciously think about compassion.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A battle most of us have already lost.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Amongst the stress, responsibility and self-obsession, we forget that guilt, shame and judgement aren&amp;rsquo;t our only options.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It&amp;rsquo;s only because we have consistently resorted to these methods, that we&amp;rsquo;ve solidified these behaviours as the go-to solution to our problems.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In the process, forgetting that life is inherently simple, and that we merely overcomplicate things in attempting to  manage the daily complexity of life.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Already though, by reading this article, you&amp;rsquo;ve done more than most to bring this concept to your attention.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And it is a huge head start ol&amp;rsquo; buddy, if you choose to maintain it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So this is today&amp;rsquo;s reminder to be compassionate.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To remain human.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;why-is-compassion-so-difficult&#34;&gt;Why Is Compassion So Difficult?&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://juliusreade.com/img/blog/18-01.png&#34; alt=&#34;Why Is Compassion So Difficult?&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Compassion is the sympathetic pity and concern for the suffering or misfortune of others.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In other words, to have a healthy consideration for those in lesser positions.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In other words, to think better of yourself.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The thing I love about compassion is that it doesn&amp;rsquo;t ask or require anything of you.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Instead, it&amp;rsquo;s about letting go of the things holding you down.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So you can be free.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;All it says is, &amp;ldquo;You should go love yourself&amp;rdquo;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;Whether life is tough or easy, love yourself regardless.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It applies when things suck. It applies when things are great. It applies always.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What&amp;rsquo;s not to like about it?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sort of like flossing, it&amp;rsquo;s one of those things we should be doing, yet we don&amp;rsquo;t.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And that&amp;rsquo;s we want to discuss.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Usually, most of us happen to discover it by chance.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;No different to thinking about someone from high school we haven&amp;rsquo;t thought about, literally ever.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Our mind goes &amp;ldquo;Holy shit, I forgot that person even existed!&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;That&amp;rsquo;s what discovering compassion was like for me, at least.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;On some level, we must admit that compassion is also somewhat of a luxury.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Although it may sound like an excuse, compassion is something that a lot of us simply don&amp;rsquo;t have the capacity to embrace.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Capacity in the sense that we have a million other pressing issues in our mind, racing past our ability to even consciously comprehend them.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So while compassion is nice, so is paying our bills or ensuring that our children don&amp;rsquo;t spill milk all over the carpet.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The time simply isn&amp;rsquo;t there.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The other issue is that in today&amp;rsquo;s dog-eat-dog world, many of us are desperate.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And as a result, many of us also feel as if we cannot be compassionate, because of the kind of nasty competition capitalism produces.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As the ever-shrinking pie dwindles to that of a crumb, and we fight over the scraps of our masters.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And I think a strong side effect of this is that compassion has become more of a response to the standards of society.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As opposed to a genuine effort to care for others.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For example, a lot of the chivalry aimmed towards women is largely mindless.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Us men don&amp;rsquo;t actually give a shit, we&amp;rsquo;re just doin&amp;rsquo; it cause society has set the standard.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;At the same time, a lot of the misogyny aimed at women is no different - we&amp;rsquo;re just doing our best to get that pie.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Which is to say that we bank on the expectations of society, rather than do what&amp;rsquo;s truly compassionate.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is human priority playing out in excess, along with the modern pressures of society.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In a world where individuals and companies vying for our attention.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Where compassion has become nothing more than a product, no different to anything else in life.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And like any successful product, exposure is essential.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So let&amp;rsquo;s expose you to our dear darling - compassion.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For the product of your emotions is much more important than the indirect means we spur to create them.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We attack at the source.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;reconnecting-through-compassion&#34;&gt;Reconnecting Through Compassion&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://juliusreade.com/img/blog/18-02.png&#34; alt=&#34;Reconnecting Through Compassion&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;ll give you to the tl;dr.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There is no easy way to be compassionate.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Literally, you just do it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I remember at Year 10 camp we had to jump off a high platform to catch a bar.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I was the first to go and I was absolutely terrified.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Then my teacher decided to go next and he&amp;rsquo;s like, &amp;ldquo;This is terrifying, how do I do this!?&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I told him that there was no point trying to rationalise it, or strategise it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You literally just jump and try your best to catch the bar.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You just do it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Will it be that easy for you? Probably not.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now it begs to state that compassion is a conscious effort.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;At least initially it will be.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It&amp;rsquo;s something you have to think about, and apply to your life and point of view.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And this begins with dissolving absolutely everything that doesn&amp;rsquo;t promote compassion in your life.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Your points of view. Your thoughts. Your feelings. The people in your life.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Throw it away.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Certainly, this is a tricky aspect that I can&amp;rsquo;t quite help you with.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I can bring it to your attention, I can tell you why it&amp;rsquo;s necessary - however only you can make that sort of commitment.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Put it this way, I disowned my own mother and it&amp;rsquo;s made a world of difference of how I feel about myself.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Ultimately, it&amp;rsquo;s about reducing that attrition - all those things in your life which make it difficult for you to forgive and feel compassion.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;While also working on consciously producing compassion in your life, piece by piece.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;At least initially it helps to focus on how you feel about yourself.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;No one is forcin you to have to love others. But life dosn&amp;rsquo;t work if you don&amp;rsquo;t love yourself.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Which is why it&amp;rsquo;s best to think of compassion as a kind of guide.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A simple philosophy to keep in your mind, that dictates a standard of how you should feel.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Because at the end of the day, compassion is a process - the process of learning to love.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And how we choose to connect and relate with reality.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;compassion-is-an-alternative-to-suffering&#34;&gt;Compassion Is An Alternative To Suffering.&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://juliusreade.com/img/blog/18-03.png&#34; alt=&#34;Compassion Is An Alternative To Suffering&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When you dive into it deeper, compassion is sort of a blanket statement for a lot of different things.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Fundamentally compassion is about forgiveness.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It is about learning to forgive ourselves, as opposed to feel bad for ourselves.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To smile at the things that make us feel sick, as opposed to repress.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To dissolve the narratives in our mind telling us that we aren&amp;rsquo;t good enough.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Certainly, it doesn&amp;rsquo;t mean that we must forgive others - although it usually helps.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It&amp;rsquo;s about how we feel about ourselves - the originator of our feelings.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And when you really focus on this message of compassion, you realise it&amp;rsquo;s about relaxation.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;About letting go of the worry in our mind.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Deconstructing all those illogical structures we&amp;rsquo;ve constructed over the years, that we relied on to &amp;lsquo;keep us safe&amp;rsquo;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Often the culprit is within us.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We trick ourselves to believe our abuse is truly helpful.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When in reality, many of us feel as if we have no choice but to consciously tolerate our own suffering.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What compassion is saying is that we have an alternative to this abuse.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Rather than hate ourselves, we can learn to love ourselves instead.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Accepting the fact that love is a valid option.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In a sense, the idea that we have an alternative to our suffering is an eerie thought, because in some ways it&amp;rsquo;s to discredit how we truly feel about ourselves.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It&amp;rsquo;s to say that our feelings are wrong, and that our suffering is meaningless.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But when you think about it, what we are doing is actually very powerful.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It&amp;rsquo;s admitting to ourselves that we have control over our emotions.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;That we don&amp;rsquo;t have to fit the narrative, that we can almost rebel against the things we believe to be truly.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Depression and being sad isn&amp;rsquo;t radical.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Finding the courage to overcome it is, because self-discovery is what true revolutionaries do.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;They question the fabric of their reality, rather than succumb to the pressures defining it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And this begins with ourself.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Not trying to appease our emotions through activism or ideology - but removing ourselves from the narrative and choosing our own unbiased path.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But rather, taking control of the way you feel about yourself, and realising what we&amp;rsquo;re ultimately capable of.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;However you&amp;rsquo;re afraid, and fear eats away at you - carving itself into your self-perception.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Compassion is here to help.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;losing-compassion&#34;&gt;Losing Compassion.&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://juliusreade.com/img/blog/18-04.png&#34; alt=&#34;Losing Compassion&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Admittedly, I&amp;rsquo;m not a very compassionate person.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;m not sure if I ever used to be, however it&amp;rsquo;s something that I can tell has gotten worse over the years.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In pursuing my goals, I&amp;rsquo;ve taught myself to detach from the people around me.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I mean, I didn&amp;rsquo;t become a complete Hitler, but I strived to protect myself more than I did to expose myself to my own vulnerabilities.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In my mind I felt it was the only way to get anything done, which made complete sense at the time.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Put simply, I was surrounded by toxic shitheads.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;People who did nothing to contribute towards my mental health.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And closing up was my way of dealing with that, even if I knew it was hurting me on the inside.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I suppose the problem is that even though those circumstances have changed, and I&amp;rsquo;ve managed to leave all these people behind - my attitude towards life still remains within hostility.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I still rely on this hatred to protect myself, which is also &amp;lsquo;protecting me&amp;rsquo; from all the goods in life as well.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Given my awareness of the situation.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Part of the consequence of this attitude is that I developed resentment towards others, rather than undesrtanding.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I merely focused on my own point of view and how I was benefiting, which although valid - provided nothing for my mental health.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Usually, my response has been to run away.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And certinly, I think that&amp;rsquo;s okay - especially if you&amp;rsquo;re running towards something else.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What it doesn&amp;rsquo;t address however, are those long slogs where you have no choice but to endure - and this is where compassion comes in.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I suppose the hardest part in this process is that a lot us weren&amp;rsquo;t taught to think this way about ourselves growing up.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Usually through harsh criticism and judgement, we instead learnt that self-criticism was the way to go.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Which isn&amp;rsquo;t to say that we don&amp;rsquo;t love ourselves, however it slowly warps us over time, and we leave behind all those positive qualities we had as a child.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This probably emphasises the importance of balance, so that we don&amp;rsquo;t entirely lose ourselves within our conquests.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Managing information and human complexity has always been one of the hardest problems for us to deal with, and inevitably concepts such as compassion are going to be lost along the way.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The idea is that by consciously thinking about compassion, even in the smallest of ways, we can reprogram ourselves to be the thing we think.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So that it can become a central part of our lives, even more so than our own focus and determination.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And when I rediscovered compassion again recently, it was pretty incredible.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Certainly, I&amp;rsquo;d become so detached from reality, that when I read about these concept of compassion for the first time in years, it managed to blow a few circuits in my mind.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In particular, self-compassion.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is about learning to love yourself, and embracing that to become even more effective as a human being.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;no-expectations&#34;&gt;No Expectations.&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://juliusreade.com/img/blog/18-05.png&#34; alt=&#34;Why Is Compassion So Hard?&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I suppose the thing I find beautiful about compassion is that it&amp;rsquo;s self-sustaining.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;No feeling sad or excessively manic at the whim of a moment.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;No falling down to find yourself unable to get back up.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It&amp;rsquo;s existence without the pressure, which I think a lot of us are afraid of.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To live without out that constant reminder, that constant nudge telling us that something isn&amp;rsquo;t quite right.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What we don&amp;rsquo;t quite realise that by not being stressed and by not worrying, we actually provide ourselves with clarity.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Only by removing these stresses, can we actually experience a kind of love that doesn&amp;rsquo;t exist without the social anxiety or expectation that you&amp;rsquo;re doing it wrong.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Of course, like most things, life is rather unforgiving.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Which is why it&amp;rsquo;s like a cycle - we do bad, we forgive, we do bad, we forgive.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Otherwise you create a complete monster out of yourself.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;!--

People make awful logicians.

One of the biggest logical fallacies we make, and one that has very significant consequences, is this idea that arguments are one dimensional. 

For example, we believe either that someone either hates us or likes us. 

Yet we don&#39;t think in the possibility that maybe it&#39;s because we hate or like ourselves. 




Instead, we&#39;re focused on the result. 

The funny thing about compassion is that it isn&#39;t difficult. 

There&#39;s nothing about compassion that doesn&#39;t make sense. 

It&#39;s literally something that just clicks in your mind. 

Yet what makes compassion so difficult is that it&#39;s an entirely foregin concept in modern society. 

We are not taught to be compassionate, and most companies view compassion as a form of weakness.

Instead, we are taught about responsibility and blame. 

Competition doesn&#39;t breed compassion. 

It&#39;s do or die - and that is something you drill into yourself. 


I suppose a more fundaental question we need to ask is why we forget to be compassionate. 

I think the answer is quite simple. 

Firstly, I think compassion is a state of mind. 

Secondly, our daily interactions aren&#39;t centered around facilitating love.

And through a slow and arduous attrition, we cultivate hatred instead. 

Because we&#39;re so worried about the result, that we don&#39;t really care how we get there. 

We simply do the thing our brains tell us to, and that drives us.

Again, consciousness.

I&#39;ll keep repeating it again, and again, and again.

That&#39;s really the whole point of this article.

To repeat the same thing in different ways, so you can feel confident about compassion.

And furthermore, understand that if I can bullshit my way through this - so can you. 




I suppose what makes it hard is that it&#39;s just a foreign concept in modern society. 

We don&#39;t live in a compassionate society. 

In my head I&#39;m stuck in this world of diminishing promises and brutal competition, and believe part of my humanity died along with it. 

Certainly, even though I knew something wasn&#39;t right with me, I merely thought it was a necessary burden in my pursuit for productivity. 



Of course, this usually only works for so long, until our underlying beliefs kick in and we activate the depression machine on full blast. 

Not days. Not months. Years.

There&#39;s no easy way around it. 

So why does it take so long? 

Put simply, love is a never-ending process and so if we&#39;re going to live for 

But put it this way, if you&#39;re going to be around for at least another 40 years or so, a few years ain&#39;t too bad. 

Buckle up kiddo&#39;, we&#39;re only gettin&#39; started.  

--&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>