<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Somebody Please Help Me</title>
    <link>https://juliusreade.com/categories/dating/index.xml</link>
    <description>Recent content on Somebody Please Help Me</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>This work is licensed under a Creative Commons Attribution-ShareAlike 4.0 International License.</copyright>
    <atom:link href="https://juliusreade.com/categories/dating/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>Why Young Men Resort To Pick Up</title>
      <link>https://juliusreade.com/2017/01/22/why-young-men-resort-to-pick-up/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Jan 2017 04:23:26 +2020</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://juliusreade.com/2017/01/22/why-young-men-resort-to-pick-up/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;!--  --&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Firstly, I&amp;rsquo;m quite impartial to pick up.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Despite the fact that pick up is willingly demonised by society, it is also a process that is widely expected of men.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Which traditionally works well&amp;hellip; except for men who are mentally retarded, socially inept or come from broken homes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You know, like myself.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Happen to lose several limbs in a horrible, though defiantly necessary war?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Forget about it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Regardless, it&amp;rsquo;s this dynamic that leads to the wide range of sexual activity here on earth, from the consensual to the prolonged jail sentence of your local pedophile.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With this in mind, it&amp;rsquo;s important to note is that there are many different &amp;lsquo;pick up&amp;rsquo; methods, in pursuit for a whole range of different reasons.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Whether for love or for random sexual encounter, it&amp;rsquo;s a dirty and risky game we all play.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Whether we like it or not.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Certainly men (and women alike) pursue pick up for all sorts of different reasons, and I have no purpose to judge their intentions.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Again, some people have some very severe issues, and that&amp;rsquo;s just one of the many nooks and crannies of modern society.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Rather, it can help to think of pick up (or perhaps &amp;lsquo;dating&amp;rsquo;) in regards to the same dynamic as religion.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You have the religious folk who do good, the extremists who use it as an excuse to reign havoc, along with a whole plethora of intentions from the innocent to the benign.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;No different to anything else in life.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I suppose I wanted to write this piece in order to paint an accurate picture of what pick up means for guys like me.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Broken, insecure, young men.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Largely because I feel my experience is quite indicative of what a lot of other guys in my position went through, including a lot of my friends.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Because for some people, it&amp;rsquo;s a necessity where the alternatives are much worse, otherwise to accept complete social-retardation for an eternity.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Okay.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I get that people like me should probably be locked away in a cupboard, forever collapsing into a pit of hysteria and withered memories.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;On the contrary I would argue that pick up is a necessary process of self-discovery for most men, that can teach them to become more confident and functional.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A process of self-discovery which can allow men to realise what they&amp;rsquo;re capable of in life, beyond the depression and general hopelessness of being a squirm.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;why-i-resorted-to-pick-up&#34;&gt;Why I Resorted To Pick Up&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://juliusreade.com/img/blog/07-01.png&#34; alt=&#34;Why I Resorted To Pick Up&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Firstly, I would like to say that pick up taught me to treat women with respect.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Wait a second.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Treat women with respect!?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;hellip;or perhaps worded more accurately, to respect myself enough not to feel compelled to pursue women.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You see, us guys are insecure, confused, somewhat broken men trying to figure out women.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Well, not even women per-say.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It&amp;rsquo;s that us guys don&amp;rsquo;t know how to connect with people.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Period.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And this includes our peers, our friends, our parents and our loved ones, and this is the real challenge we&amp;rsquo;re trying to overcome.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As a result, pick up literature more-or-less taught me everything positive I know about women.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Which is really drastic when you think about it, but let&amp;rsquo;s talk about why.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Firstly, I hated people.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I was a cynic who thought society was bullshit, and thought everyone was fake and phony.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As you can imagine, this extended quite readily towards women given how different they are from men.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Furthermore, I didn&amp;rsquo;t meld well into groups of any sort.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I was basically this angry, socially-incapable, unapproachable blob of human shit - and it wasn&amp;rsquo;t attractive to anyone.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A large portion of this hate derived from the belief I held of relationships, as the most horrible, completely unnecessary evil ever created.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Which in part had to do with my family growing up (or perhaps lack thereof).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I didn&amp;rsquo;t really grow up with a loving, happy family. My parents were constantly fighting and they eventually split when I was eight years old.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I even remember telling my parents as a child that I never EVER wanted to be in a relationship because of how horrible it was.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Which of course was interpreted as meaningless childish gibber.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But fuck, that&amp;rsquo;s how I actually felt.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It&amp;rsquo;s fair to say my irrational hate for women grew as an extension of my relationship with my mother.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;She is best described as an irrational pit of back-handed judgement that would attract questionable men.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In particular, drunken, abusive men who loved to fight and argue, or perhaps had no choice dealing with my mother.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Oh, and disconnected men with money, because obviously that&amp;rsquo;s how you form perfectly healthy relationships. /sarc&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So as you can imagine, I didn&amp;rsquo;t grow up with strong, sensible female role models.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Which of course, you don&amp;rsquo;t realise until you&amp;rsquo;re much older.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Not to mention, all her relationships were seemingly transactional and this invaded my idea of what a relationship was, or at least should have been.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Because it wasn&amp;rsquo;t about love or what you had in common.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It was about what you could provide, largely in the form of security and money.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And the worst thing is that this even extended to the relationship I had with my own mother.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Everything in my life was an expectation that rided upon my own success in life, which is the perfect formula to breed quiet, insecure young men.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We very rarely talked, let alone hugged unless if it was forced and we didn&amp;rsquo;t eat dinner together or any of that stuff normal families do.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And of course, she wasn&amp;rsquo;t the only one.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Almost everyone in my life was dysfunctional, but that&amp;rsquo;s just how it was for a very premature Julius Reade.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;On the bright side, pornography addiction can almost solve anything - so good for me!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;misconceptions-of-pick-up&#34;&gt;Misconceptions Of Pick Up&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://juliusreade.com/img/blog/07-02.png&#34; alt=&#34;Misconceptions Of Pick Up&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If it&amp;rsquo;s one thing I&amp;rsquo;ve learnt, it&amp;rsquo;s that humans are opportunitists.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We crave opportunity, whether to prove ourselves or to simply gain insight into something unknown.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And insecure young men are prime opportunitists.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Opportunitists because it&amp;rsquo;s something they don&amp;rsquo;t understand, and it&amp;rsquo;s the mystery that drives you to compel.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We don&amp;rsquo;t know any women. We don&amp;rsquo;t have any sexual experience, let alone the confidence or skills to make it happen - and it&amp;rsquo;s such a cluster fuck that it makes you want to smile.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In a way it&amp;rsquo;s a sick, reinforcing cycle that drives you to work harder and turn your dreams into a reality.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Of course, those who obsess the most over pick up also risk staying within the realm of their dreams, never actually pursuing their desires in the real world.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Instead of actually developing the confidence required to approach women, they merely fantasise about having confidence, which is why most men who study pick up are harmless.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A bunch of dreamers with crass undertones.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Which brings me to my first misconception: There&amp;rsquo;s this idea that the people who study pick up are the ones being assholes to women.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I want to assure you that this is largely not the case.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Because the reality is, 95% of the people who end up reading pick up literature never actually approach women.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Remember. Hopeless dreamers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;That is us.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Rather, it&amp;rsquo;s the existing assholes who are&amp;hellip; well, being themselves.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Secondly, pick up advice taken from literature is very rarely used in practice.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When you&amp;rsquo;re in the moment, looking a girl in the eye, you&amp;rsquo;re too nervous to be able to even comprehend what you should be doing.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If anything, most pick up advice is nothing more than fantasy porn for men, like a shot of prefabricated confidence to the head.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Of course, that&amp;rsquo;s not to say that there aren&amp;rsquo;t effective pick up systems out there.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It&amp;rsquo;s just that they mostly serve as an extension of your own fantasies and ideals, rather than as a complete solution you follow word-by-word.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Not to mention, part of the fun of dating is simply being yourself.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thirdly, please understand that pick up books can&amp;rsquo;t help you overcome the gargantuan aspect of trial-and-error that is understanding women.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;At best these books can help you set expectations of women, and in a lot of cases, incorrect expectations that merely make you more insecure and retarded.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Because when you&amp;rsquo;ve rarely interacted with women in your life, you&amp;rsquo;re going to crumble regardless of what you read.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And the more you crumble, the more self-conscious you become which inevitably drags you down into a very hefty pit of sorrow.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You develop all these stupid ideas of what it&amp;rsquo;s going to be like. You sell yourself these fantasies of how amazing it will be, only to realise it&amp;rsquo;s not your fantasies in the slightest.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So you begin over-questioning what could have gone wrong, in most cases further attaching yourself to your fantasies, in addition to detaching yourself from the reality of dating.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We become human pineapples.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;good-and-bad-pick-up-literature&#34;&gt;Good And Bad Pick Up Literature&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://juliusreade.com/img/blog/07-03.png&#34; alt=&#34;The Good And Bad Of Pick Up Literature&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Like anything, there&amp;rsquo;s good and bad pick up literature.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Most people start off with the soul-destroying pick up that is well-marketed, only to discover the true gems later down the road once it&amp;rsquo;s too late.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Initially, pick up taught me that women were dumb fuck-things.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;That if you played &amp;lsquo;the game&amp;rsquo; well enough, you could get anyone you want.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Of course, it&amp;rsquo;s just horrible, highly-marketed just ego-porn that provides no feasible advice on how to build confidence or sustain positive relationships with these &amp;lsquo;fuck-things&amp;rsquo;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The most popular book a lot of us started out with was &amp;lsquo;The Game&amp;rsquo; by Neil Strauss, which I&amp;rsquo;m sure most guys have read at some point in their lives.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I believe the reason why we start out with this kind of pick up literature, is because a) We honestly don&amp;rsquo;t know any better and b) Broken, insecure men largely equate relationships, and more importantly our self-worth, with sex.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You see, we didn&amp;rsquo;t really grow up with the hugs, or the sensible father figures to guide us in life, so we instead turned to our instincts to guide us for help.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Which following a decade of pornography addiction, can easily develop into the belief that dating and relationships are all about sex.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You think in your head that because pornography is so amazing, that having sex is probably ten times better.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It&amp;rsquo;s hilarious how we set ourselves up for failure.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;At this point, you&amp;rsquo;ll probably have experienced a few toxic and heart-breaking relationships, in addition to a handful of dilipidating sexual encounters, that has now turned you into a literal shell of a human being.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And it&amp;rsquo;s usually at this point that you discover the pick up literature you probably should have read to begin with.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Unique advice that has very little to do with women or even sex.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Rather, excellent advice that focuses on developing self-confidence, as well as this idea of what it means to be a man.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One of the best books I read was called &amp;ldquo;Models: Attract Women Through Honesty&amp;rdquo; which basically talks about self-confidence.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I remember reading the first chapter and being completely shocked, as it literally described, word-by-word, why all my previous interactions with women were toxic.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It delivered such an incredible amount of clarity to my life, and I highly recommend it for people dealing with a bad breakup.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Quite powerful stuff.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;pick-up-makes-you-insecure&#34;&gt;Pick Up Makes You Insecure&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://juliusreade.com/img/blog/07-04.png&#34; alt=&#34;Pick Up Makes You Insecure&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What I find incredible is how I almost went from not caring about women at all, basically hating women, to becoming highly insecure about not having a girlfrined or active sexual partner, overnight.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I think it&amp;rsquo;s because pick up becomes this horrible self-reinforcing cycle.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Once you begin to experience the constant rejection and difficulty of pick up, it makes you feel incredibly insecure about yourself and you develop the belief that it&amp;rsquo;s because you&amp;rsquo;re not good enough.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Which compells you to try harder, which merely develops into more insecurity and you literally melt into the ground and sow into the soil.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So you begin questioning yourself and your ability to attract females and one thing I became incredibly insecure about was my race.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I thought because I was Asian that nobody wanted to date me and it was stupid.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Quite ironically, and a huge part of the problem, is that a lot of broken men turn to pick up because it offers a form of hope.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;From their depression. From their problems.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Essentially, it gives them ambition and something to aspire to in life, which when you&amp;rsquo;re binge eating junk food and smoking weed everyday, seems quite the dandy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The problem is that depressed people with mental illness aren&amp;rsquo;t suited to deal with the pressures of dating.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We take things too personally. We can barely handle our own emotions and in the process, we end up becoming more insecure and more depressed about ourselves.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Because ultimately we&amp;rsquo;re just chasing another dream in our head.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Like a lot of delusions in life, we essentially create this wild fantasy of what it will be like in our head, which carries our ambition forward.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Then once you experience the reality of the situation, it detaches you and crushes you.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Of course, men cannot possibly know what ambitions in life are worth chasing, especially if they grew up on a diet of pornography and video games.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Who knows, perhaps I would have been better off with a strong father figure.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Though perhaps on a deeper level, the problem is in thinking that we can discover love within dating, when really it is something that must come from within ourselves.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;HA.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;#YOLO&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;the-problem-of-dating&#34;&gt;The Problem Of Dating&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://juliusreade.com/img/blog/07-05.png&#34; alt=&#34;The Problem Of Dating&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Ultimately, I think pick up is used as a scape goat for what is essentially the problem of dating.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Dating is hard, especially in today&amp;rsquo;s modern society.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I mean, we think it&amp;rsquo;s getting easier because of things like the internet and Tinder, but ultimately these are broken systems which can tend to complicate things further.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;People feel weirded out when you approach them in public, yet they also feel detached from the hundreds of profiles they see online, due to the sheer volume of participants online.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In addition, dating is often this exclusive club that can be dictated by our friend groups or our position in society, which can be jarring a lot of people.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The only advice I have is to try something different.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I personally used Tumblr as a platform for dating and that&amp;rsquo;s how I found my current long-term partner.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Regardless, it&amp;rsquo;s always going to be messy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;ALWAYS.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But it&amp;rsquo;s a necessary process and it&amp;rsquo;s better to suffer now, rather than later.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;m 24 as of writing this article and I honestly couldn&amp;rsquo;t even imagine dating  again.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;m so pre-occupied with my career and my ambitions that it would be a huge set-back for my life.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Of course, each to their own.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We all have our own agenda and this is merely mine, scribbed across your screen in illegible Australian.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;!--

Ultimately, I believe most ambitious young men will get involved with pick up literature to some extent.



A lot won&#39;t because they won&#39;t need it, but a lot of guys from broken homes will, and it&#39;s a dangerous combination when you think about it. 




In particular, I want us to focus on this idea of victim and what it actually means to be a victim. 

Because when you dig down deeper, it&#39;s a silly, self-perpetuating notion that provides no utility in trying to understand who we are. 

It&#39;s like trying to pick a victim between two countries at war. It merely adds fuel to the fire. 



Because there&#39;s this tendency in society to glamourous and romanticise things, such as high-end professional gambling or even mental illness, and pick up is no different. 

What&#39;s interesting is that no matter what our pursuit in life, our basic needs as a humans never change and yet we feel compelled to take these arduous routes in order to validate our self-worth. 

We spends thousands of hours trying to master something, when all we really needed was a hug and some self-reassurance. 

More to come later.  



I think once you experience a few dozen dysfunctional boyfriends and pseudo step-fathers, in addition to the constant fighting and drunken disorderness, being jaded really is a positive outcome.


Now admittedly, a lot of pick up is ugly. 

A lot of people end up getting hurt on both sides and it&#39;s entirely unavoidable.

So let&#39;s talk about it, rather than dismiss it or demonise it. 


Of the pick up systems I studied, there was one book that stood out.

Vin de carlo&#39;s pandora&#39;s box. 

What I really liked about it is that accurately explained women from a relationship and sexual motivation point of view. 

Ultimately as part of the &#34;system&#34; there are eight types of women when it comes to dating.

I won&#39;t go into detail, however it&#39;s quite fascinating and it works. 



There are two types of fools in this world. 

There are those who try to escape reality by distracting themselves with menial pleasures, such as television and video games. 

It is a kind of surreal adoption of passivisty towards life, where there is no urgency or drive. 

In the other corner, are those who are so fearful and insecure that they have this intense need to pursue reality.

To change, aspire and explode. 

I happen to fall into the second category, as do most other people who pursue pick up artistry. 


Men so insecure that we feel like we need to study this stuff. 

In addition, as young men without higher, purposeful ambition or responsibility, chasing sex seems like the next best thing.


--&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>