<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Somebody Please Help Me</title>
    <link>https://juliusreade.com/categories/success/index.xml</link>
    <description>Recent content on Somebody Please Help Me</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>This work is licensed under a Creative Commons Attribution-ShareAlike 4.0 International License.</copyright>
    <atom:link href="https://juliusreade.com/categories/success/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>Understanding My Invalid Obsession With Success</title>
      <link>https://juliusreade.com/2017/04/30/understanding-my-invalid-obsession-with-success/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Apr 2017 11:33:26 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://juliusreade.com/2017/04/30/understanding-my-invalid-obsession-with-success/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;!--
mental-health-strategy-is-an-odds-game
This is how you create broken men
Today I Am Unhealthily Preoccupied With Success
My Unhealthy Obsession With Success
My Delicate Obsession With Success
My Delicate Obsession With Success
My Invalid Obsession With Success
My Unscientific Obsession With Success

My Unreasonable Obsession With Success
--&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I strongly suspect that my drive for success has a strong connection with my mental illness.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Part of me also feels as if I don&amp;rsquo;t have a choice.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The difference being that when I&amp;rsquo;m not pursuing success of some kind, my brain instead switches and dedicates itself towards pursuing failure.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Which arguably is much worse.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For some reason, there is no healthy middleground in my mind. Interally I am always fighting for something, so it may as well be for my improvement.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Of course, there&amp;rsquo;s also the monster that pursuing success turns me into, which solves none of the equally disconjunct aspects of my personality.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I remain just as detached, anti-social and obsessive in my trials to achieve my goals, and like a heavy addiction, it carries me without mercy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;However is that necessarily a bad thing if it is helping me achieve positive outcomes?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Maybe the obsession is just a bonus to my condition.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After all, it&amp;rsquo;s what allows me to remain engaged when the going gets tough, and maintain any sense of hope in the relentless batter that is unrecognised self-study.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Which could mean that there&amp;rsquo;s nothing wrong with me after all.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Yet I can&amp;rsquo;t help but ponder.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Have I been so traumatised in my past life as to be like this?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Obviously.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I suppose I&amp;rsquo;m stuck in a sort of fatal totality here, in which I can&amp;rsquo;t quite gauge my delusion because it&amp;rsquo;s what keeps me productive and above water, so-to-speak.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Those dainty safe-guards keeping me in place.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;become-the-12-step-program&#34;&gt;Become The 12-Step Program&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://juliusreade.com/img/blog/13-01.png&#34; alt=&#34;Become The 12-Step Program&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;m not entirely sure why I&amp;rsquo;m writing this article, however I think part of it is that I want to remove the stigma surrounding success.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I suppose there are two stigmas which both hurl itself at each other like a bunch of drunk sailors:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Mental illness and success.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For whatever reason, you&amp;rsquo;re viewed as a pompous asshole when you tout your achievements, yet you&amp;rsquo;re also equally as broken for admitting you have mental health issues.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Well fuck that.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I think it&amp;rsquo;s a product of misunderstanding, so hear me cry as I provide my perspective on the whole thing.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Success isn&amp;rsquo;t something magical.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It&amp;rsquo;s not a magic trick you pull out your ass.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It&amp;rsquo;s literally nothing more than a regime you follow, which you stick with and commit to.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The idea behind becoming obsessive is so that you can develop a love-affair with your routine, so that your goals and ideals are the only thing you percieve in your mind, as the antitode to your insanity.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The way you do this is through your routine (I like to refer to it as my programming), which I suppose is achieved via a number of effective systems to prevent the subject (myself) from breaking down under all the pressure and stress.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For example, this blog forms one part of this overall programming effort, and it&amp;rsquo;s been great for me.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It sort of serves as a cognitive lubricant that allows me to stay focused and true to who I am.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;These words are designed to program myself to succeed, not only in what I write, however also the in the commitment to ensuring that these words are being delivered every 2 weeks.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It&amp;rsquo;s a program that benefits my mental health, no difference to attending a number of private therapy sessions.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I just like it my way.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The idea of the program is simple: It is designed to teach perseverance and structure.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Because the truth is, I&amp;rsquo;m not well.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But I&amp;rsquo;m doing well.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And that&amp;rsquo;s all that matters, because even though part of me feels shrouded by guilt and shame and depression and all these awful things, I&amp;rsquo;m still above water.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thanks to my program.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Rather than allow these negative aspects of my life drown me, I work towards managing them in a healthy way, and I think my pursuit for success is enabling, rather than all-out disgusting.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The hard part is convincing myself when the programming fails, which is what usually leads to relapse, where I actually do revert back to my broken, unadjusted self.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Which I assure you, helps absolutely no one.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;the-effects-of-a-shitty-childhood&#34;&gt;The Effects Of A Shitty Childhood&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://juliusreade.com/img/blog/13-02.png&#34; alt=&#34;The Effects Of A Shitty Childhood&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I didn&amp;rsquo;t choose my shoes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Society did for me.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now I want you to picture a young, ambitious Julius.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;He&amp;rsquo;s got a pretty fantastic face and he&amp;rsquo;s being told he can achieve anything in life.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Hell, that&amp;rsquo;s the message I&amp;rsquo;m sure all us kids recieved - largely due to the inability of our parents to prove it themselves.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;Young Julius, you&amp;rsquo;re incredibly smart. You have so much potential to achieve anything you want. Except me, I still earn peanuts which is why we&amp;rsquo;re having cardboard for dinner tonight.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Not that young Julius actually cared about achieving anything.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;All he could think about was the dopamine-sucking video games he wanted to play, because unfortunately our young Julius is living in a paradox.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The problem is that young Julius was not taught the value of hard work.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In addition to being told he was special, entrenched the idea that he was naturally better than everyone else.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Which worked because I was better than everyone else&amp;hellip; until it didn&amp;rsquo;t, and that&amp;rsquo;s when I really began to struggle in high-school.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For example, I don&amp;rsquo;t think I completed a major assignment until 4th grade.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For some reason, my mother thought it would be a brilliant to take control of the damn thing, and complete the project herself.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Reason being that it would be inherently better, allowing me to have better marks.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Which of course, left me in the dust. I mean, I wasn&amp;rsquo;t a complete idiot, however I certainly wasn&amp;rsquo;t reaching my full potential.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In addition to that, let&amp;rsquo;s also imagine being told that you&amp;rsquo;re not good enough.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Imagine being told by your own mother that you&amp;rsquo;re not good enough, everyday for the rest of your life.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To make things worse, she thinks it&amp;rsquo;s okay because she&amp;rsquo;s not saying that exact words.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Instead, it&amp;rsquo;s in the  tone of her voice. In her constant dismissal and backhanded compliments.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Part of it is never telling you what a wonderful job you&amp;rsquo;ve done.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Instead, it&amp;rsquo;s about constantly telling you that you could have done better.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Which I imagine is designed to push you to try harder, however the net effect is that you feel as if you&amp;rsquo;re not enough.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Ultimately, it turns you into a cynic which slowly eats away at you, to the point where you no longer feel comfortable communicating yourself in fear of being judged.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I suppose that&amp;rsquo;s why I never had a close relationship with my mother. Because I wanted to keep myself distant from her words.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Worst of all?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Through the constant judgement you learn to judge yourself.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You learn to hate yourself, because you genuinely feel as if you&amp;rsquo;re not good enough, and it grows inside you like a cancer.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now when you pair this pessimism with feeling like you&amp;rsquo;re special&amp;hellip; you create people like me.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I mean, you can literally say goodbye to your life right there.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Because you won&amp;rsquo;t have any normal friends, or be able to sustain healthy relationships, or have a loving family life.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Unless of course you choose to fight for it, which is why I&amp;rsquo;m here, writing this blog today.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I have a lovely girlfriend, I know exactly what I want with my life, and I take care not to allow my inner-pessimism to take control.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;the-millenial-factor&#34;&gt;The Millenial Factor&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://juliusreade.com/img/blog/13-03.png&#34; alt=&#34;The Millenial Factor&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The glaring problem with young Julius is that he&amp;rsquo;s been setup for failure.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;He&amp;rsquo;s driven towards success and achievement through his own false idealisation of himself, yet he&amp;rsquo;s also incapable of delivering the goods.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;That&amp;rsquo;s why he has issues, or at least used to.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Part of the reason why I still have issues is that I&amp;rsquo;m still trying to fight this idea in my mind that I&amp;rsquo;m not good enough or that I&amp;rsquo;m not capable.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Which isn&amp;rsquo;t so bad because after all these years, I&amp;rsquo;ve finally managed to understand the value of hard work.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And that&amp;rsquo;s taken me 95% of the way towards solving my mental health issues.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I suppose the problem is that although people can adjust, ultimately we don&amp;rsquo;t change.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I still get depressed and triggered for the very same reasons that I did ten years ago.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The only difference is that now at 24 years old, I now know how to medicate myself effectively.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Initially the self-medication began with replicating success through dopamine, and my gosh, the ways you can do that is incredible.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Pornography was made me feel incredibly successful, if only temporarily.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Gambling made me feel successful for a while, but the drawbacks nearly ruined me, which is why I stopped.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Marijuana helped me forget everything, which is always a bonus.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Yet the best medication I&amp;rsquo;ve found thus far has been to pursue my goals and ambitions in a controlled, and sensible manner.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In other words, to pursue hard work.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The side-effects aren&amp;rsquo;t nearly as having a cigarette at 3am in the morning, but it works.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Which I suppose brings me to my original point:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I don&amp;rsquo;t really have a choice.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Throw on top the inherent difficult of life, not to mention the severe disadvantage of millenial life, and I&amp;rsquo;ll need as much drive and help as I can get.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There are literally no available entry-level jobs for our skills set. None of us can afford to buy a home, let alone have children.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And it&amp;rsquo;s only going to get worse.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So what choice do I honestly have other than to be obsessed with my work, in order to have better opportunities in life?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We don&amp;rsquo;t.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We honestly don&amp;rsquo;t, other than to accept that there is no hope and that is something I cannot accept.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So I will continue to grind until I&amp;rsquo;m able to afford the things I want.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Of course, I also enjoy it and is part of the reason I&amp;rsquo;ve been able to go on for so long.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The only thing I worry about is when I actually have the freedom to stop being obsessed, once I have my career and family sorted.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Perhaps it never will.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;!--
### We Are A Product Of Society

![We Are A Product Of Society](/img/blog/13-04.png)

So these are the things that happen when I do not commit to the program. 

And yet the program is clearly not perfect. 

It has occassional glitches that cause my perception of myself to revert and break down.

Where I look at myself and don&#39;t feel convinced. 

That you&#39;re nothing more than a phoney, and that it&#39;s all one big lie you tell yourself to...

and this is where I forget. 

I become so enthralled into the programming that I forget why I&#39;m here, who I am, and so I destroy it all in the hopes of starting again. 

It is learning through regret, because my mind has forgotten the importance of program. 

The good news is that I&#39;m learning to program myself in more effective ways, in the hope that I stay fully within my bubble of dream and aspiration.

For example, I have this thing where I think about my future children. 

And that in large part drives me to study and try harder and not try and screw myself over.

The plan is that by being an expert at X and Y I&#39;ll essentially be able to work from home and avoid the expensive costs of childcare etc.

So that that they can have an amazing life and not make the same mistakes that I have.

I want three lovely, outstanding children. 

In part to create a loving family, because it&#39;s something I lacked growing up. 

As if it&#39;s going to create peace in my life. To have people to talk to and take care of. 

I mean, am I stupid for wanting this? Is it superficial? 

Perhaps, but programming is inherently superficial and is all I really have to carry me forward. --&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;we-are-a-product-of-society&#34;&gt;We Are A Product Of Society&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://juliusreade.com/img/blog/13-05.png&#34; alt=&#34;We Are A Product Of Society&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I often wonder how things would be I were just be normal.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But I can&amp;rsquo;t.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In fact, I&amp;rsquo;m not even sure if I&amp;rsquo;d want to, because there&amp;rsquo;s a kind of balance or harmony in life at the moment that&amp;rsquo;s serene.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Things are working out for this guy, and I know it&amp;rsquo;s because of who I am.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I know it&amp;rsquo;s because of my obsession with success that I&amp;rsquo;ve been able to pursue all the opportunities in my life.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I doubt I would have gotten through all those awful jobs if it weren&amp;rsquo;t for my aspiring to become something more.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It&amp;rsquo;s also corrupted me to some extent.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I mean, I&amp;rsquo;m at a point in my life where other people no longer interest me, and I&amp;rsquo;m not sure if that&amp;rsquo;s normal or if it&amp;rsquo;s because I&amp;rsquo;ve become so engrained&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It&amp;rsquo;s like I just don&amp;rsquo;t&amp;hellip; see value in them, when I could be studying or working instead.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Maybe I&amp;rsquo;m just an addict in disguise.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;!-- 

Yes, I&#39;m still broken. 

But if I can fix myself nearly as fast, it&#39;s almost like I can convince you that I&#39;m normal, while also having my slice of the cake. 



I think I&#39;m at the point where 

 I&#39;m literally always working or studying or reading and I wonder if I&#39;m going insane. 

As time drifts by, I can&#39;t help but feel more and more detached from reality. 


--&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>