<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title></title>
    <link>https://juliusreade.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>This work is licensed under a Creative Commons Attribution-ShareAlike 4.0 International License.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 09 Oct 2016 10:23:15 +1100</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://juliusreade.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>My Incredibly Unhealthy Obsession With Success</title>
      <link>https://juliusreade.com/2017/04/30/my-incredibly-unhealthy-obsession-with-success/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Apr 2017 11:33:26 +1100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://juliusreade.com/2017/04/30/my-incredibly-unhealthy-obsession-with-success/</guid>
      <description>I feel as if my drive for success has something to do with my mental illness.
Not necessarily in an inherently bad way (nothing is inherently bad, nor good), but that my obsession is driven by my inadequacies and insecurities.
&amp;hellip;rather than a kind of purity or kindness that perhaps only exists in the land of fairtales.
Part of me feels as if I&amp;rsquo;ve been so traumatised as to be violently pushed towards a direction of success, rather than out of free-will.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Self-Awareness: The Two-Step Tango</title>
      <link>https://juliusreade.com/2017/04/16/self-awareness-the-two-step-tango/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Apr 2017 11:33:26 +1100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://juliusreade.com/2017/04/16/self-awareness-the-two-step-tango/</guid>
      <description>Self-awareness is hard.
It&amp;rsquo;s like a two-headed medusa that knows all your password combinations and spits fire at you, sort of like an ex.
Okay.
Clearly that&amp;rsquo;s a poor comparison, but as you can tell it&amp;rsquo;s something that continues to frustrate me.
Self-awareness is hard because it takes a lot of patience and experience to make work, and even then it&amp;rsquo;s not guaranteed to protect you from your own weaknesses.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Success Is A Verifiable System</title>
      <link>https://juliusreade.com/2017/03/31/success-is-a-verifiable-system/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Mar 2017 07:23:26 +1800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://juliusreade.com/2017/03/31/success-is-a-verifiable-system/</guid>
      <description>Maybe you&amp;rsquo;re a struggle sport.
An undefined blob of human misery, awaiting death in a slurry of shame and complete unanticipation.
Maybe you feel unable to help yourself become successful, either due to lack of knowledge or ability to strive.
That&amp;rsquo;s right.
Welcome to the human experience.
With your host, the shitty human experience co-ordinator.
Perhaps it&amp;rsquo;s because you feel fearful or possibly shameful of the potential outcome, producing anxiety via your own self-perception.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Non-Postal</title>
      <link>https://juliusreade.com/2017/03/16/non-postal/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Mar 2017 03:23:16 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://juliusreade.com/2017/03/16/non-postal/</guid>
      <description>I haven&amp;rsquo;t been posting lately.
And it&amp;rsquo;s entirely your fault.
Naturally I&amp;rsquo;m going to blame you and absolutely anything or anyone else but myself, because of the kind of blight that seeps from your personality like a derelict, sunken ship.
So please allow me to try and paint that glorious picture, that honed nautical possession of fluctuating visual image, which I&amp;rsquo;m sure you&amp;rsquo;ll prize more than the explicitly gorgeous Mona Lisa.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What It Means To Be An Effective Adult</title>
      <link>https://juliusreade.com/2017/02/19/what-it-means-to-be-an-effective-adult/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Feb 2017 03:23:16 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://juliusreade.com/2017/02/19/what-it-means-to-be-an-effective-adult/</guid>
      <description>Millenials like myself are retarded.
We have all these false expectations of what life should be, and in believing so strongly in the advice that has been thrown at us, have failed miserably to cope with the harsh reality of&amp;hellip;
&amp;hellip;not becoming the next big thing on YouTube.
Yep. That&amp;rsquo;s me.
Despite being &amp;lsquo;adults&amp;rsquo; many of us fear commitment, rely too heavily on our parents for financial support, and fail to kickstart our careers in any meaningful way.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>An Intuitive And Simple Guide To Understanding Your Depression</title>
      <link>https://juliusreade.com/2017/02/08/an-intuitive-and-simple-guide-to-understanding-your-depression/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Feb 2017 11:33:26 +1100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://juliusreade.com/2017/02/08/an-intuitive-and-simple-guide-to-understanding-your-depression/</guid>
      <description>The aim of this article is to help you come to terms with your depression.
Ummmm, say what?
Don’t fret, you lucky puck.
I promise it won&amp;rsquo;t involve intense emotional gouging, followed by hours of soul-destroying questioning of your precious most-inner thoughts.
Except that it probably will, so stay tuned.
As you can imagine, depression is a heavy topic with a lot of thorny edges poking at the sides.
Which is why this article won&amp;rsquo;t focus on a number of topics that are vital to understanding depression.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why Young Men Resort To Pick Up</title>
      <link>https://juliusreade.com/2017/01/22/why-young-men-resort-to-pick-up/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Jan 2017 04:23:26 +2020</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://juliusreade.com/2017/01/22/why-young-men-resort-to-pick-up/</guid>
      <description>Firstly, I&amp;rsquo;m quite impartial to pick up.
Despite the fact that pick up is willingly demonised by society, it is also a process that is widely expected of men.
Which traditionally works well&amp;hellip; except for men who are mentally retarded, socially inept or come from broken homes.
You know, like myself.
Happen to lose several limbs in a horrible, though defiantly necessary war?
Forget about it.
Regardless, it&amp;rsquo;s this dynamic that leads to the wide range of sexual activity here on earth, from the consensual to the prolonged jail sentence of your local pedophile.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Have You An Effective Communication With You And Me</title>
      <link>https://juliusreade.com/2017/01/08/have-you-an-effective-communication-with-you-and-me/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Jan 2017 21:39:46 +1600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://juliusreade.com/2017/01/08/have-you-an-effective-communication-with-you-and-me/</guid>
      <description>Let&amp;rsquo;s talk communication.
You know, that one thing many of us fail at miserably.
&amp;ldquo;Great forehead bro, cause it makes me wanna cream like fat Tuesday&amp;rdquo;.
If it&amp;rsquo;s one thing I&amp;rsquo;ve learnt it&amp;rsquo;s that all our traumatic experiences and toxic relationships in life can be attributed to this thing called &amp;lsquo;communcation&amp;rsquo;.
&amp;hellip;or precisely, lack thereof.
When we lack communication between people, we create a number of false assumptions and expectations, that crush us when we realise they&amp;rsquo;re not who we think they are.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Please Don&#39;t Tell Me You&#39;re Sorry</title>
      <link>https://juliusreade.com/2016/12/25/please-dont-tell-me-youre-sorry/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Dec 2016 16:12:30 +1534</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://juliusreade.com/2016/12/25/please-dont-tell-me-youre-sorry/</guid>
      <description>Today we&amp;rsquo;re going to try something new.
Sparkling new.
And for some people this is going to be difficult.
Partly due to the disconnect of reading an article over the internet, as one of the many billions of thoughtless &amp;ldquo;see-things&amp;rdquo; you will probably wade through today.
Apologies in advance for not being physically available in the room with you.
Though not all hope is lost.
What this article CAN probably do for you, is make you that tiny bit more aware of how seemingly useless you are.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Smart People Don&#39;t Think. They Plan Ahead</title>
      <link>https://juliusreade.com/2016/12/11/smart-people-dont-think.-they-plan-ahead/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Dec 2016 16:12:30 +1534</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://juliusreade.com/2016/12/11/smart-people-dont-think.-they-plan-ahead/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;ve managed to develop a lot of dumb habits over the years.
Stalking. Self-harm. Self-obsession. Addiction. Irrational idealisation.
The kinds of habits developed by unadjusted people, because we&amp;rsquo;re stupid and don&amp;rsquo;t seem to know any better.
Ultimately, the cycle itself is fairly basic:
The dumb habit is developed, we assume everything is horrible, and we deny all responsibility and control over the situation.
We fuck up and crave some more, craving and craving until the cows come home.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why Obtaining A Full-time Job Should Be Your Number One Priority</title>
      <link>https://juliusreade.com/2016/11/27/why-obtaining-a-full-time-job-should-be-your-number-one-priority/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Nov 2016 14:53:55 +1100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://juliusreade.com/2016/11/27/why-obtaining-a-full-time-job-should-be-your-number-one-priority/</guid>
      <description>Committing towards a full-time job is one of the most fundamental things you can do in life to secure your future success.
Not because of the money or the tireless hours spent making someone else rich.
Those things are inconsequential to the true benefits of working full-time. Benefits which are incredibly difficult to replicate in other systems.
Blah. Blah. Blah.
Though perhaps you already know this.
Perhaps you&amp;rsquo;ve already experienced first-hand the crushing resilience that full-time work forces upon you.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What It Means To Be A Porn Addict</title>
      <link>https://juliusreade.com/2016/11/13/what-it-means-to-be-a-porn-addict/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Nov 2016 11:33:26 +1100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://juliusreade.com/2016/11/13/what-it-means-to-be-a-porn-addict/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m a pornography addict and quite frankly, it sucks.
I decided to write this article in order to provide some closure into what happens in my mind when I go full addict.
Because even though it&amp;rsquo;s an issue most men face and widely accept, I personally believe it&amp;rsquo;s not okay.
So rather than brush it over, I&amp;rsquo;m choosing to address it for the betterment of myself and society.
As always, addiction is an incredibly intimate and personal experience that touches us all in different ways.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Intuitive Explanations Make You Dizzyingly Smart</title>
      <link>https://juliusreade.com/2016/10/30/intuitive-explanations-make-you-dizzyingly-smart/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Oct 2016 11:33:26 +1100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://juliusreade.com/2016/10/30/intuitive-explanations-make-you-dizzyingly-smart/</guid>
      <description>You&amp;rsquo;re not stupid.
Gullible, probably. Delusional? Well, obviously.
I mean you&amp;rsquo;re on this website designed for misfit derelicts, which clearly indicates that there&amp;rsquo;s something very wrong with you.
Yet I don&amp;rsquo;t think you&amp;rsquo;re stupid.
Because as long as you have the ability to learn, you cannot possibly be stupid.
Your ability to learn is what makes you more powerful (and in a lot of cases, more irrational) than any other animal on this planet.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Services</title>
      <link>https://juliusreade.com/services/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Oct 2016 10:23:15 +1100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://juliusreade.com/services/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://juliusreade.com/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Oct 2016 09:54:24 +1100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://juliusreade.com/about/</guid>
      <description>#About</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Writing</title>
      <link>https://juliusreade.com/writing/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Oct 2016 09:54:24 +1100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://juliusreade.com/writing/</guid>
      <description>#About
rst rst
rs tsr strst</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The child who watched anime…………</title>
      <link>https://juliusreade.com/adelaidesucks/the-child-who-watched-anime/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Nov 2007 13:10:30 +0934</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://juliusreade.com/adelaidesucks/the-child-who-watched-anime/</guid>
      <description>Something i wrote during music:
“Damn it” I shouted. Although it was a happy moment, I stared in disgust. “What the hell……….go clean yourself up”. Alex looked down and cried but I showed no signs of sympathy. “Make sure you wash around your pants as well”. He knew that he was in trouble.
As Alex walked out of the room, cheers of laughter and triumph were heard. Alex knew clearly that he was unwanted, in a gay sort of way.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why the hell is it so hot? (And this time it isn&#39;t me)</title>
      <link>https://juliusreade.com/adelaidesucks/why-the-hell-is-it-so-hot-and-this-time-it-isnt-me/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Nov 2007 18:23:30 +0934</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://juliusreade.com/adelaidesucks/why-the-hell-is-it-so-hot-and-this-time-it-isnt-me/</guid>
      <description>As i look outside my front porch, i see people covered in flames; melted tar stuck to there faces screaming: &amp;ldquo;Help!!!! Help!!!! I&amp;rsquo;m on fire&amp;rdquo;, and no matter how many times i see it happen, i still break into laughter, but why is it so damn hot outside? Or maybe a better question to ask: Why do i continue to wear long pants and shirts with sleeves? Well as we all know (from my past experiences with the media), i have a too large a profile, which means that ANY revealed part of my body would cause much tension between the paparazzi whether to put it on page 1 or 7.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Save as a draft</title>
      <link>https://juliusreade.com/adelaidesucks/save-as-a-draft/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Nov 2007 10:18:30 +0934</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://juliusreade.com/adelaidesucks/save-as-a-draft/</guid>
      <description>As a kind and loving person, you may be aware that there is also another side to me. Whether it may be my recent claims that the &amp;ldquo;Pham organization&amp;rdquo; are evil, or the fact that i am hot, we must now realize that there are other role models in life that can deliver far more than what i can offer. Further examples prove that not only am i unworthy, but also a person that hates reading and socializing with girls.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Influence of Jane</title>
      <link>https://juliusreade.com/adelaidesucks/influence-of-jane/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Nov 2007 11:42:30 +0934</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://juliusreade.com/adelaidesucks/influence-of-jane/</guid>
      <description>Ignorant, racist, unfair. Just some of the words to describe a particular people, or also known as &amp;ldquo;The People of Pham&amp;rdquo;. Through out the years, people have struggled, but why? Up until now, we have discovered the real culprit and his minions and the fact that they have been among us the whole time.
Many theories suggested that global warming was to blame, but HARD EVIDENCE PROVES that it was actually one of the many evil leaders in the &amp;ldquo;Pham&amp;rdquo; organization.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Role model for 2007.</title>
      <link>https://juliusreade.com/adelaidesucks/role-model-for-2007./</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Nov 2007 21:52:30 +0934</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://juliusreade.com/adelaidesucks/role-model-for-2007./</guid>
      <description>Despite the fact that this blog most definitely not keeping you informed with issues that matter, i think as a people we can say i have extraordinary talent from within. But as much as i can brag about myself, i also have the ability to work miracles, that even make the worthy cry. Which brings me to my unrelated issue&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;.my upcoming top ?? list which will contain the essentials components to functional music.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>One Blog. Two Outcomes.</title>
      <link>https://juliusreade.com/adelaidesucks/one-blog.-two-outcomes./</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Nov 2007 21:52:30 +0934</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://juliusreade.com/adelaidesucks/one-blog.-two-outcomes./</guid>
      <description>May i please say (Although i have all right to say this that) there can be no equal outcome with the exsistence of this blog. Thus there are two main outcomes that either you or I must suffer. These are:
 You come to my blog and you add on to the total number of visitors to this site. This results in me being happy and you having to suffer the &amp;ldquo;bad comedy&amp;rdquo; of my articles.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Non-Update 3#</title>
      <link>https://juliusreade.com/adelaidesucks/non-update-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Nov 2007 21:11:30 +0934</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://juliusreade.com/adelaidesucks/non-update-3/</guid>
      <description>Lol&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;..If you look at my stats the number of visitors have gone down by one each day (sorta). Also I know that i have so called &amp;ldquo;viewers&amp;rdquo; but i cant be certain, (According to the stat counter). If you are one please place i comment in the comment thing
Thx
Ps: i have AT LEAST one. (Probaly Bryan)
 Nice try Alan, you have no evidence&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My Adventures as a level one mage..........</title>
      <link>https://juliusreade.com/adelaidesucks/my-adventures-as-a-level-one-mage........../</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Nov 2007 14:25:30 +0934</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://juliusreade.com/adelaidesucks/my-adventures-as-a-level-one-mage........../</guid>
      <description>Under my Maplestory account (Until i realised it was possibly the worlds worst game), i adventured through the land of MapleStory, (or what ever it was called) and began the legacy which was me. As i entered the portal to the new land, i was confronted with what many would call a &amp;ldquo;blue snail&amp;rdquo;, which looks easy enough to kill. Which is when i came to my common senses&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;..
Up until this point i pity the fools who play that game, as it is truly a boring and unpleasant experience.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Another one of my ****ing guides..............</title>
      <link>https://juliusreade.com/adelaidesucks/another-one-of-my-ing-guides............../</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Nov 2007 09:44:30 +0934</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://juliusreade.com/adelaidesucks/another-one-of-my-ing-guides............../</guid>
      <description>This week (or at least i think so), i will be guiding many unguided Australian&amp;rsquo;s (people) that have been struggling with exams and etc. However, you&amp;rsquo;re probably asking, why the **** are you telling me after my exams? Well even miracle workers, such as myself can&amp;rsquo;t answer that question, which is why we move on to the first step.
Cheat. Although i don&amp;rsquo;t encourage cheating, i do &amp;ldquo;ADVISE&amp;rdquo; that you TRY it out *wink* **wink**.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Non Update #2</title>
      <link>https://juliusreade.com/adelaidesucks/non-update-#2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Nov 2007 19:32:30 +0934</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://juliusreade.com/adelaidesucks/non-update-#2/</guid>
      <description>But that doesn&amp;rsquo;t matter because no body reads this shit anyway :)&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;..</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Non-Update</title>
      <link>https://juliusreade.com/adelaidesucks/non-update/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Nov 2007 13:52:30 +0934</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://juliusreade.com/adelaidesucks/non-update/</guid>
      <description>Haven&amp;rsquo;t posted/updated lately because of exams. And can&amp;rsquo;t until exams r over :)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I hate anime.............. [Part 2]</title>
      <link>https://juliusreade.com/adelaidesucks/i-hate-anime..............-part-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Nov 2007 15:44:30 +0934</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://juliusreade.com/adelaidesucks/i-hate-anime..............-part-2/</guid>
      <description>Today we will be looking at ways to suppress the anime movement and anime enthusiasts in general. For help i asked Doctor George Flanagan and he told me that there are 3 main steps. Quote: &amp;ldquo;Remember Julius, there are three main steps&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;&amp;quot;, too bad i forgot what he said afterwards which is why i Made up my own: Refuse, Convince, Tazer.
The First step is to Refuse any of the persons requests, e.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I hate anime..............</title>
      <link>https://juliusreade.com/adelaidesucks/i-hate-anime............../</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Nov 2007 02:54:30 +0934</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://juliusreade.com/adelaidesucks/i-hate-anime............../</guid>
      <description>Imagine a concept worse than aids. Worse than the possibility of death and boredom in a cartoon&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;..
Or you could just watch anime?
Short for &amp;ldquo;I am gay&amp;rdquo; in Japanese, anime has inspired many to become freaks of nature, often looking for help in secluded areas. But why do people enjoy watching it? Are people becoming so desperate? Or am i just making this up?
I asked Psychologist Tim Regan, and he told me some shocking figures.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Top 177 Song List</title>
      <link>https://juliusreade.com/adelaidesucks/top-177-song-list/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Oct 2007 18:30:30 +0934</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://juliusreade.com/adelaidesucks/top-177-song-list/</guid>
      <description>Updated Randomly&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;
I am Damn sick of people who say they listen to good music&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;..
&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;..Which is why i have created this blog to show the losers in society about MUSIC. But here are some question first:
-Do you want to be gay at school (or the workplace)?
-I am a complete retard?
-I have no friends and want to remain this way?
-I am still breast fed by my dad?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Julius how to guide.............</title>
      <link>https://juliusreade.com/adelaidesucks/julius-how-to-guide............./</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Oct 2007 14:57:30 +0934</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://juliusreade.com/adelaidesucks/julius-how-to-guide............./</guid>
      <description>Now as we all know, my personal fan base in South Korea has been requesting for a guide on &amp;ldquo;How to get laid&amp;rdquo; which is why i prepared a little something earlier on&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;.
 There are many reasons why people don&amp;rsquo;t get laid, but here are the reasons why you should:
 It forces you to read this guide, which means absolutely nothing. Saves you money each Friday night. Provides a near impossible challenge, from reading this guide.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Top 252 song List (Updated)</title>
      <link>https://juliusreade.com/adelaidesucks/top-252-song-list-updated/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Oct 2007 12:08:30 +0934</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://juliusreade.com/adelaidesucks/top-252-song-list-updated/</guid>
      <description>The list had Been updated, with songs and fixed up. Enjoy.
I also strongly encourage that you try and download MOST OF these songs legally. (Wink Wink, Nudge Nudge). But then again, my friend was telling me about A little program called Limewire&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;
Overall, if you do download them (which would take a long time) you should like a majority of the songs (depending on whether you are a music freak like me, or a loser in society&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Suggested Websites</title>
      <link>https://juliusreade.com/adelaidesucks/suggested-websites/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Oct 2007 11:18:30 +0934</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://juliusreade.com/adelaidesucks/suggested-websites/</guid>
      <description>Ummmmm also, you might need these&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;.. http://gctracker.mine.nu:800/index.php - Gamecube isos ( Torrent) www.fat-pie.com - The only reason why i can&amp;rsquo;t get to sleep&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;. www.fat-pie.com/jerryjackson.htm - U must not forget this&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip; http://www.deeko.com/store.asp - The only place to buy games online&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;..
 http://melbournehighschool.editboard.com/index.htm - Forum, can&amp;rsquo;t remember what happened to it though&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;.oh wait i got suspended? http://mhsforums.17.forumer.com/ - Actual working one, surprised though&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;.. http://downloads.khinsider.com/ - For the nerds&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;.video game nerds&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;.. http://seehere.blogspot.com/ - A much better Blog&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://juliusreade.com/1/01/01/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://juliusreade.com/1/01/01/</guid>
      <description>I eat paleo and here&amp;rsquo;s why I&amp;rsquo;m not crazy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://juliusreade.com/1/01/01/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://juliusreade.com/1/01/01/</guid>
      <description>You are above the guilt.
If it&amp;rsquo;s one feeling I identify with most, it&amp;rsquo;s probably guilt.
It&amp;rsquo;s like this visceral tar that runs through my veins and infects everything in my mind.
At it&amp;rsquo;s worst, the guilt becomes absolutely paralyzing.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>