<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title></title>
    <link>https://juliusreade.com/categories/emotion/index.xml</link>
    <description>Recent content on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>This work is licensed under a Creative Commons Attribution-ShareAlike 4.0 International License.</copyright>
    <atom:link href="https://juliusreade.com/categories/emotion/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>Two Philosophies</title>
      <link>https://juliusreade.com/2017/07/09/two-philosophies/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Jul 2017 08:31:26 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://juliusreade.com/2017/07/09/two-philosophies/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;p&gt;I have two simple philosophies that help guide me through life.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;rdquo;&amp;hellip;the inconsequential bread and butter of our human experience.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Hopefully you can find them useful.
&lt;!--Perhaps they can be of use to you. --&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I suppose I would call them &amp;lsquo;recession philosophies&amp;rsquo;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Philosophies designed to carry you through hardship, and assist you in overcoming the surreal harshness of reality.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Because the problem is that the system can no longer support itself.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Which means many people are losing out, in particular, younger generations like myself.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In the year 2017 it&amp;rsquo;s literally impossible to find work, let alone be able to afford the opportunities of past generations - such as home ownership.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And it&amp;rsquo;s only getting worse by the day.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You can be fully-qualified, over-qualified, or the best damn technical or cultural fit possible.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It literally doesn&amp;rsquo;t matter - the work simply isn&amp;rsquo;t there.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I made it to a final-stage interview at an amazing company, only to have the position turned down because they were worried they&amp;rsquo;d have to fire me again in three months.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It&amp;rsquo;s hard, but this kind of lackery requires you to maintain hope under extreme pressure.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In other words, to learn to suffer gracefully.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And that&amp;rsquo;s how having a few fine-tuned philosophies in life can really help.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Because when you embrace the suffering, you become impenetrable.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Personally speaking, I don&amp;rsquo;t take too much notice of these philosophies anymore.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Initially I would consciously think about them in times of desperation.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;However now my brain has been wired to just get shit done.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Ultimately, because I understand that I lessen my human experience by not following these guidelines, as well as reduce what I&amp;rsquo;m ultimately capable of.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In essence, these two philosophies are predominantly designed to help promote achievement, without the resounding guilt or judgement.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Note: Without the resounding guilt or judgement.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Because while a lot of us know how to be successful.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Very few of us know how to do it without also developing an addiction or dragging our ego along for the ride.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Don&amp;rsquo;t be that person.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;philosophy-one&#34;&gt;Philosophy One.&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://juliusreade.com/img/blog/17-01.png&#34; alt=&#34;Life is hard, so you may as well make it harder.&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My first philosophy is about resilience:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Life is hard, so you may as well make it harder.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It relies on this premise that life is inherently hard, and that it&amp;rsquo;s never going to get easier.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Which is to say that life will always be sufferable, regardless of which path you take.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The aim of this philosophy is to highlight this idea that there&amp;rsquo;s no fear or harm in pushing yourself to your limits.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Because when life is already hard, making it more &amp;lsquo;difficult&amp;rsquo; for the time being will have literally zero impact on your life.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So bloody hell, don&amp;rsquo;t be a dickhead and pursue all the meaningfully difficult paths in life, because at least you&amp;rsquo;ll grow from it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;#YOLO&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;lsquo;cause let&amp;rsquo;s face it, folks.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A lot of life is pretty fucking awful.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Most of the time we just don&amp;rsquo;t realise it because we&amp;rsquo;re so exhausted, stressed and under pressure, that we don&amp;rsquo;t even have time to process the suffering.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Let me tell you.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Waking up at 5:45am each morning because the rent is too damn high to live any closer to work, just ain&amp;rsquo;t normal.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And even though I&amp;rsquo;m used to it, part of me wishes I didn&amp;rsquo;t have to.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So honestly, what difference is it going to make lifting unbearably heavy weights to point of bodily cramps, or bunkering down for a few hours to learn something useful that may even bore you to death?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Precisely.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There really isn&amp;rsquo;t any.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And that&amp;rsquo;s what motivates you to choose the inherently more difficult path.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Because when you&amp;rsquo;re already bathed in pain, painful choices become easy to make.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So where do most people go wrong?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;They fail themselves in assuming that some forms of suffering are worse than others.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;They ultimately cannot understand that working out or trying to better themselves isn&amp;rsquo;t the only thing that sucks in life.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Everything else sucks too.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The cake you&amp;rsquo;re currently eating sucks, because it&amp;rsquo;s making you unhealthy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sitting and watching TV sucks, because it&amp;rsquo;s making you dumb.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It all sucks, and yet people have preference as to what sucks more.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I suppose part of this comes down to awareness.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With this understanding that life will never get easier, you become aware of the fact there&amp;rsquo;s consequences not only in your actions, however also in your existence.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And that you&amp;rsquo;re always going to pay, one way or another.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you choose the &amp;lsquo;easy&amp;rsquo; option, you essentially lose out in gaining any insight into the human experience - which is a form of suffering.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Yet if you choose the &amp;lsquo;hard&amp;rsquo; option, you still have to suffer to claim your reward.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The suffering in both cases is exactly the same, because the consequences are equal.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And when everything in reality sucks equally, your experience becomes dictated by time.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Rather than effort.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Which is to say that as long a you commit your time to suffering meaningfully, you&amp;rsquo;ll be fine.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The key point here is that by normalising your suffering, you normalise the choices in your life.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And it allows you to begin viewing life in terms of possibility.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Rather than with doubt or fear.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Instead of viewing something as a challenge, it merely becomes another task dictated by choice and time.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Pretty cool, ey?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;On a more fundamental level, this philosophy is about choice and embracing the cause and effect of life.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Certainly, it helps me tremendously when I don&amp;rsquo;t feel like working out, or I&amp;rsquo;m feeling a bit lazy in the haze of depression.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It helps rationalise the challenge, pressure, ambition and stress I put myself under each day, without throwing the baby out with the bath water.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;philosophy-two&#34;&gt;Philosophy Two.&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://juliusreade.com/img/blog/17-02.png&#34; alt=&#34;Everyone experiences and goes through the same thing.&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My second philosophy is quite similar in what it aims to achieve, although it approaches the issue from a different angle.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;(Come to think about it, I feel like these philosophies are quite nhilistic, though I&amp;rsquo;m certainly no philosophy literature whiz-bang.)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Everyone experiences and goes through the same thing.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This one is beautiful.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I suppose it&amp;rsquo;s a counter-balance to the first philosophy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What it&amp;rsquo;s essentially saying is that everyone suffers and experiences the same kind of suffering.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In other words, that there is absolutely nothing special or unique about you, what-so-ever.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In that everyone experiences happiness, sadness, guilt, shame and everything else inbetween.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To the same relative degree.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We all feel that same relative level of anxiety when we approach an interview, or ask a stranger out to a date.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We all feel that initial lack of dread when the thought of having to workout pops in our head.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We all want to binge on dopamine and escape from reality.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Everyone is fucked.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We&amp;rsquo;re all inherently the same, and we all experience the same bullshit in trying to achieve greatness.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The only thing that&amp;rsquo;s truly different is in how we choose to react, and that&amp;rsquo;s what this philosophy is trying to highlight.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This philosophy is tremendously helpful, because it aims to dissolve what you think and feel about yourself.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And help you realise that your emotions, your feelings and your understanding of the world isn&amp;rsquo;t inherently special.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And therefore, aren&amp;rsquo;t a real threat or influence on how you decide to live your life.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In essence, what it&amp;rsquo;s really saying is that you shouldn&amp;rsquo;t take your feelings, thoughts or emotions personally, because dey r knot reel.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Therefore, allowing you to push through those difficult feelings as something external, not internal to who you are.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Essentially, everyone is normal.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Which a lot of people take to mean average, however that&amp;rsquo;s only assuming that you think you&amp;rsquo;re special (assuming you take an optimistic approach towards this quandry).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Instead, it highlights this wonderful idea that to be normal, is to have the opportunity to grow and become great.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It embraces this notion that everyone is normal and that from there, they decided to become something more.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The same, normal, fucked-up, retarded, fundamentally flawed human being, all trying and failing at the same time.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Ultimately, it denotes the imporance of hard work, as well as embracing your own responsibility to dictate our success in life.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It is what allows us to truly understand that life is an level-playing field, relative to our position.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And the only thing stopping you, is your lack of willingness to suffer.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;le-close&#34;&gt;Le Close.&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://juliusreade.com/img/blog/17-03.png&#34; alt=&#34;Everyone experiences and goes through the same thing.&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So there you have it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In summary, life is hard and everyone experiences that same hardness.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It acknowledges that every one of us faces the same challenges each day, and that we have choice in how we choose to deal with those challenges.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Bon appetite.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;!--

Not that anyone really thinks about their own personal philosophies, nor adopts the philosophies of others. 

It&#39;s just something you tend to discover when you try to put into words what motivates you and makes you tick. 

--&gt;

&lt;!-- 




I&#39;ve been thinking a lot about the personal philosophies I follow in my life, because they&#39;re something I rely on heavily.

Of course, previously I&#39;d always thought that personal philosophies were bullshit. 

To me they were meaningless preamples that had no value, beyond a temporary confidence boost that would fade as quickly as it had arrived. 

In retrospect I realise it&#39;s because I hadn&#39;t discovered any philosophies that were truly personal, nor applicable to myself and the challenges I was facing in life.

Which is to say that these two philosophies may not be applicable to you. 

Both of these philosophies relate to each other in different ways. 

The two philosophies I live my life by are:

&#34;Life never gets any easier.&#34; 

&#34;Everybody goes through and experiences the same thing.&#34;

Okay. 

I get it.

You&#39;re probably as completely underwhelmed, just as I am right now. 

And trust me, it sounded a lot cooler in my head, but 

I&#39;ll explain the significance of these philosophies, however first I want to talk about what philosophies are and how to make the most of them. 

Before then, just a really, really quick primer on what philosophies are and how I use them.





### Philosophy #1: Life Never Gets Any Easier

![What Are Personal Philosophies?](/img/blog/07-01.png)

This is probably the philosophy I rely on the most. 





### What are personal philosophies? 

![What Are Personal Philosophies?](/img/blog/07-01.png)

I rely on my philosophies 


When I&#39;m in a difficult situation, I can rely on these two philosophies to provide me with confidence in my choices. 


It can help to think of personal philosophies as simple reminders. 

Nothing more. Nothing less. 

You don&#39;t have to live your every, single moment according to a philsophy .

Persoally 


A couple of weeks ago I was hanging out with a friend in the city.

I usually enjoy these catch-ups because it usually devolves down into a prolonged pseudo-therapy session of anxiety and self-angst, where we usually exchange trumatic episodes from our lives.

In addition, it proves I&#39;m not a complete social recluse, as I extend my frail hand towards the door knob leading to the front door - cowered in complete fear.

Regardless, we were talking about our lives and discussing what personal philosophies we live by, and I managed to come up with two different philosophies that really help me get through life.

Which I will obviously reveal soon. 



I don&#39;t really know what to think of philosophies. 

I think part of the problem is that they&#39;re inherently personal. 

While it&#39;s not something a lot of us think about, adulthood is an important part of growing up. 



I&#39;ve been thinking about this a lot lately.

About what it means to becoming this thing that is expected of people, as if it&#39;s some kind of natural progression we&#39;re supposed to embrace. 

Certainly, the idea of becoming an adult is silly.




It&#39;s an attitude we have. 



What it means to be an adult. - Be an adult 95% of the time.  My main definition is that it means to do everything your power to better your children. It means improving yourself and being all the traits you’d like your children to be. It is a self-realisation that your future generations are more important than you are, and that you must do everything in your power to support them - even if they aren’t alive yet. Most people don’t have this realisation until after they have a girlfriend, or until they actually have a child. The smart ones figure it out early. Of course, I wasn’t that smart and I figured it out waaaaaaay later. 

Responsible adults pursue success. That is an important fact to consider. 


I have two very simple philosophies in life. 


--&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Your Emotions Are An Elaborate Lie</title>
      <link>https://juliusreade.com/2017/06/11/your-emotions-are-an-elaborate-lie/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Jun 2017 08:31:26 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://juliusreade.com/2017/06/11/your-emotions-are-an-elaborate-lie/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;!-- 
Mental Illness Has Always Been A Problem Of Emotion
Your emotions are an elaborate lie. 

--&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Mental illness has always been a problem of emotion.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We either feel too much, too little, or not at all.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As a result, many of us end up losing context of our emotions and falling into the wonderful world of mental illness.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A glorious realm where nothing makes sense, and making poor, somewhat regretable decisions seems so damn right.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Obviously, there are many different ways we can end up losing context of our emotions.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Our emotions can encapsulate us to the point that we no longer feel like functioning as responsible, productive adults.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Instead, choosing to live in a kind of volatile, caustic bubble dictated by reaction and insecurity.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In other cases, people can feel so little that they no longer know how to feel at all.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Turning into gullible, easily persuaded guinea pigs, as they chase trends in a desperate attempt to feel absolutely anything.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Regardless, when you lose context of your emotions, you lose your ability to control yourself and act within your best intentions.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In fact when you think about it on a very basic level, life is nothing more than a game of managing emotion.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In order to achieve and create change&amp;hellip; or not.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In a sense, that&amp;rsquo;s why I believe it&amp;rsquo;s possible to prevent burnout from excessive effort.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you can feel the right amount of emotion and sustain that, while also maintaining your drive, then you can just about achieve anything.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;(Obviously it&amp;rsquo;s not easy, but we&amp;rsquo;re not here to do easy.)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Often the simpliest way to know when we&amp;rsquo;ve lost context of our emotions is if we feel unable to change how we feel.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Which often takes place in moments of intense hatred or sadness.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Where we feel so utterly convinced that what we&amp;rsquo;re feeling is permanent.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Causing us to no longer question our actions.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;Yes, eating an entire block of chocolate was totally the right thing to do.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Certainly, part of what makes these emotional reactions feel so real is in how they can suddenly overtake us.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As if ignited by a spark, engulfing us in flames.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In reality, these emotions don&amp;rsquo;t just appear out of nowhere.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;They&amp;rsquo;re constructed over a number of smaller agreements that we gradually create into a gargantuan, complex agreement.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;An agreement so complex and insane, that it makes us feel trapped within our emotions.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In part, because the complexity makes us feel clueless as to how we can dismantle the hundreds of smaller agreements that we&amp;rsquo;ve created.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And which all reinforce each other, turning us into silly putty.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It&amp;rsquo;s often the reason why it&amp;rsquo;s too late to control our emotions once we have an episode.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Because the stage has been set, and you&amp;rsquo;ve been cast as the crazy, old white man with shotgun.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;While there are many ways we can approach this hivemind of complexity, today I want to start simple.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I want to explain what emotions are, as well as why they&amp;rsquo;re not so scary.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In other words, to provide you with context as to what your emotions actually are.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So you don&amp;rsquo;t feel so silly or hopeless the next time you find yourself &amp;ldquo;triggered&amp;rdquo;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And it all begins with a simple analogy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;emotions-are-like-traffic-lights&#34;&gt;Emotions Are Like Traffic Lights&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://juliusreade.com/img/blog/16-01.png&#34; alt=&#34;Emotions Are Like Traffic Lights&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I really like this analogy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Mostly because I came up with it, but hopefully it clicks with you too.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I absolutely promise it&amp;rsquo;ll be more infectuous than the chlamydia currently growing inside you.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Ultimately, emotions can be thought of as traffic lights.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Traffic lights, for the unaccquianted, are those red and green lights you see at intersections, which tell cars whether they can turn or move forward.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Ingenious. I know, right?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Though when was the last time you actually sat down to think about traffic lights?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Probably never.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Even if so, it probably isn&amp;rsquo;t something you consciously and frequently think about (unless if it&amp;rsquo;s part of your work, or is an actual hobby of yours).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In fact, no one really thinks about traffic lights all that much.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;They&amp;rsquo;re simply there. At the intersection. Doing their thing.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And that&amp;rsquo;s that.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The reason being that you have this intrisic understanding in your mind that they&amp;rsquo;ll simply work.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;No different to the electricity flowing through the city or the water running through the pipes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And in most cases, they usually do.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So rather than think about traffic lights, you&amp;rsquo;re probably thinking about this person you have a massive crush on, or some deep and meaningful topic like post-modern existentialism.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In your mind, this is how life is supposed to be - and that&amp;rsquo;s perfectly fine.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I mean, I would largely agree.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Yet what happens when the power goes out and the traffic lights stop working?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Well, if you&amp;rsquo;re driving on the road, you&amp;rsquo;ll probably start taking notice of the cars around you.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And when you reach an intersection, you&amp;rsquo;ll realise that the traffic lights aren&amp;rsquo;t working.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now most people will continue to drive, in the process communicating with other drivers and being cautious, in the hope of getting to where they need to be.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Even though they realise they&amp;rsquo;re in a pickle, they also understand that it&amp;rsquo;s important to safely get to their destination.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So rather than freak out and decide not to drive at all, they instead understand that by taking things slow and being mindful of what they&amp;rsquo;re experiencing, they have nothing to worry about, no matter how tough it may be.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The fact is, they&amp;rsquo;re prepared.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;However these are not all drivers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There are some who shut down, who feel afraid, who feel unprepared - and who choose not to drive to get to where they need to.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;These people are us.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;sending-the-wrong-signals&#34;&gt;Sending The Wrong Signals&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://juliusreade.com/img/blog/16-02.png&#34; alt=&#34;Sending The Wrong Signals&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In essence, our traffic lights are fucked.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Life has tinkered with our emotions - and now nothing is working as intended.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It&amp;rsquo;s a bad place to be in, however let&amp;rsquo;s explore it further.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If we compare our emotions to traffic lights, then there really are two states our traffic lights can be in.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Much like the example above, the power can be cut off and they can stop working entirely.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is comparable to feeling too little at all.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Alternatively, they can be malfunctioning and sending us the wrong signals.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is comparable to feeling way, way too much.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Often, a lot of us tend to fluctuate between the two.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When the traffic lights are off and not working, it makes us feel confused and helpless.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We don&amp;rsquo;t know what to do, because our emotions aren&amp;rsquo;t indicating what we should be feeling.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It is what makes us feel empty and alone, affecting our motivation and general will to live.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;On the contrary when we are feeling too much, too much sadness or too much anger (and even happiness can lead to delusion).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Our traffic lights can malfunction and send us mixed signals, telling us to go forward when we shouldn&amp;rsquo;t, or turn into incoming traffic.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Which is how accidents, disasters and self-harm begins.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thankfully there are solutions.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The reason why I like comparing our emotions to traffic lights is that when you think about it, they cannot necessarily prevent us from moving forward.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sure, they may be telling us not to move forward - however that doesn&amp;rsquo;t mean that we can&amp;rsquo;t just put our foot down on the pedal and zoom ahead.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now arguably this can be a poor idea, especially if the traffic lights are working as intended.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;However in times of a crisis, we must learn to think for ourselves and understand when we can or cannot ignore our traffic lights.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Arguably it&amp;rsquo;s only because we put faith into our traffic lights that we feel unable to change.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now obviously it&amp;rsquo;s scary questioning our traffic lights, especially when we may have relied on them for so long.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;However learning not to take them personally, and understanding that they are external to our ability to change is one half of the battle.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Being able to actually do that is the other half.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;reinterpreting-our-emotions&#34;&gt;Reinterpreting Our Emotions&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://juliusreade.com/img/blog/16-03.png&#34; alt=&#34;Reinterpreting Our Emotions&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Learning to externalise our emotions is a good place to start.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In order to do this, we must also understand why our emotions are important.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As well as how we can embrace them, and our feelings as a whole.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Ultimately, our aim should be to achieve a balance so that we don&amp;rsquo;t feel too little or too much.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Provided that suffering is largely caused by a disparity in emotion.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We use our emotions to know when it&amp;rsquo;s okay to feel safe, when we should be afraid, when we should feel guilt, amongst a whole range of other feelings.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And when our emotions stop sending us the right signals, we can actually begin to think that there&amp;rsquo;s something wrong with us.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Taking it personally and downing three bottles of wine to dampen the mood.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Classy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Ultimately, emotions can be thought of as specialised indicators.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Much like traffic lights, they&amp;rsquo;re designed to guide us towards making the &amp;ldquo;right&amp;rdquo; decision.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;Feeling sad? I know, I&amp;rsquo;ll adopt an optimistic attitude and refrain from pursuing my addictions, because it will make me feel worse later&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The problem is that a lot of us didn&amp;rsquo;t learn how to make that right decision.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Instead, the narrative went a little more like: &amp;ldquo;Feeling sad? Well maybe if I starve myself and get really skinny, I&amp;rsquo;ll like, feel better about myself?&amp;rdquo;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Through our own interpretation of our emotions, we began reinterpreting the meaning of those green and red lights, beyond which they were originally intended.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is the human curse.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To take reality so personally that we no longer become human anymore.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I suppose the big difference between driving a car through a set of broken traffic lights, and the conscious human mind.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Is that the immediate urgency or danger of neglecting our emotions does&amp;rsquo;t become apparent until much later.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We don&amp;rsquo;t necessarily risk death when we ignore our emotions or proceed with a pessimistic mindset.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Often, the feedback is small if not neglible - unlike winding your body around a tree at 100km/ph due to your vague drowziness.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The issue is that these problems or reinterpretations arise over time, as we slowly reinforce these behaviours into our mind.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It&amp;rsquo;s never the first time you told yourself you&amp;rsquo;re worthless. It&amp;rsquo;s the 20,000th time that finally puts the nail in the coffin.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Ultimately, it&amp;rsquo;s the idea that through small agreements, we create large.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;seeing-through-the-red-and-green-illusion&#34;&gt;Seeing Through The Red And Green Illusion&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://juliusreade.com/img/blog/16-04.png&#34; alt=&#34;Seeing Through The Red And Green Illusion&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The beautiful thing about our emotions is that they&amp;rsquo;re merely indicators.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Which is to say that they&amp;rsquo;re nothing more than a simple feeling, until we provide it with context.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It&amp;rsquo;s funny how context can dramatically change the meaning of what we&amp;rsquo;re interpreting.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If we believe someone is innocent then we can let them get away with anything, however if we believe they&amp;rsquo;re conspiring against us, then we ensure that they feel hell.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Because the truth is, meaning and value are created through our own beliefs and interpretations of reality.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In the overall scheme of things, this provides us with two options moving forward:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We can either detach our emotions from our beliefs and expose them for what they are - indicators.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Alternatively, we can change our interpretations so that they no longer provide our emotions with meaning.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In other words, to no longer take our emotions personally, or to change how we feel about them.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The first angle provides us with immediate results, while the second method provides us with long-term results.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Both are nearly impossible.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Which is why there&amp;rsquo;s a third option.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Rather than trying to work with our emotions, we can stop listening to our emotions altogether.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;While this sounds quite radical, in practice it promotes basic self-awareness.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Rather than listen to your emotions, you instead observe your emotional state and refrain from getting involved.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It works because it keeps you out of the fight. It allows you to truly see yourself for what you are.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To assist this, I often find it helps to imagine yourself stepping away from your body, as if you&amp;rsquo;re watching yourself from a 3rd person point of view.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Because trying to communicate with malfunctioning traffic lights doesn&amp;rsquo;t help. They don&amp;rsquo;t actually care about you or have your best interest in mind.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;They don&amp;rsquo;t even realise you&amp;rsquo;re there.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;They&amp;rsquo;re simply malfunctioning in their own world.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Which is why you need to get out.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;don-t-think-and-rationalise&#34;&gt;Don&amp;rsquo;t Think And Rationalise&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://juliusreade.com/img/blog/16-05.png&#34; alt=&#34;Don&#39;t Think And Rationalise&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Unlike traffic lights, our emotions are reinforced by good behaviour.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The better you behave, the better our emotions will function.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;On the otherhand, trying to talk to yourself out of your emotions, at least I find, doesn&amp;rsquo;t help.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Because you end up engaging with yourself from a 1st person point of view, which merely solidifies what you&amp;rsquo;re feeling.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thinking your way out of your emotions also usually doesn&amp;rsquo;t help.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The problem is that the act of thinking engages with your beliefs which merely reinforces and makes you more attached to your emotions.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Observation on the other hand is designed to detach yourself.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Another aspect to consider is how we can best gauge reality.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If not for our emotions, then what?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When traffic lights go down, we still have other references to navigate through reality, such as our vision.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Which is no different to when our emotions go haywire.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is similar with when we lose sense of our emotions.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I suppose this explains the idea behind not taking things personally.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To take something personally, is ultimately to provide your emotions with power and to legitimise them.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Which really is to treat the broken traffic light before us as a source of truth.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Also known quite suitably as delusion.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And it&amp;rsquo;s no wonder, because emotion is a very powerful thing.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It&amp;rsquo;s the number one tool we use to gain trust and respect, as well as to convey our intentions.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Though I&amp;rsquo;m sure you already know this.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Oh god, this article is a complete illiterate mess lol.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I will try to fix it up when I have the time.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;!--

They&#39;re certainly more cautious and they&#39;re communicating with other drivers and giving way, however little has changed for them.


Humans are emotional creatures. 



Which means the best way to gain trust is by 



Not that change is easy, which is why most people end up staying in their abusive relationships indefinitely. 

On other side of the coin are people who have remained stationary for so long that they no longer know how to drive.

Which is to say that even inlieu of functioning traffic lights, still would be unable to get to where they want to be. 

Largely relating to people who feel too little at all. 

The worst part is that it&#39;s self-reinforcing.

Most people don&#39;t even realise they&#39;re doing it, and it often reaches a point where they think this is actually who they are - nothing. 

Which is how people end up with a BMI of 800 or develop an incredibly judgemental attitude - these outcomes are reinforced over decades, one thought at a time.

The other consequence of this slow trickle, this gradual build up, is it makes us oblivious to how we got there in the first place.

Because we don&#39;t take notice to how we got there. We simply become triggered and it encapsulates us to the point of no return. 

Of course, I can&#39;t imagine thinking ourselves out of this situation is going to be of much help. 

Which is why we need a few tricks to snap ourselves out of it.




In reality, they&#39;re merely providing us with cues for what we should do. 

Rather than control the car that is us. 

--&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>