<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Somebody Please Help Me</title>
    <link>https://juliusreade.com/categories/melbournesucks/index.xml</link>
    <description>Recent content on Somebody Please Help Me</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>This work is licensed under a Creative Commons Attribution-ShareAlike 4.0 International License.</copyright>
    <atom:link href="https://juliusreade.com/categories/melbournesucks/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>The missing words</title>
      <link>https://juliusreade.com/sydneysucks/the-missing-words/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Jun 2008 17:05:30 +0934</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://juliusreade.com/sydneysucks/the-missing-words/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Back in the office, one of my co-workers asked me what the word &amp;lsquo;happiness&amp;rsquo; meant, but i didn&amp;rsquo;t have a clue. None of our friends could figure it out too, but it somehow reminded me of my wife and kids. If only they were still alive.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I spent all of today trying to figure out the particular word, but still no clue. I tried looking it up in the dictionary, but it wasn&amp;rsquo;t there. I guess some things will just remain a mystery, although I&amp;rsquo;m sure that the word was just made up. Yes, that&amp;rsquo;s right, it was all just a prank. I&amp;rsquo;ll get that bastard!!!! I&amp;rsquo;ll make up words too, like &amp;lsquo;joy&amp;rsquo; and &amp;lsquo;anger&amp;rsquo;. Yes, that will teach that bastard to mess with my emotions&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Julius Reade&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;I just sorta had a great idea, which became this article&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;..&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I hate anime.............. [Part 8]</title>
      <link>https://juliusreade.com/sydneysucks/i-hate-anime-part-eight/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Jun 2008 16:15:30 +0934</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://juliusreade.com/sydneysucks/i-hate-anime-part-eight/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Whenever anybody makes a reference to anime or has the need to bring up Naruto in a conversation, I tell them to get fked and eventually I&amp;rsquo;ll walk away. But sometimes, it&amp;rsquo;s not that simple. What if they apologise and promise to give you $50? Do you take the money and thank them, or do you refuse their offer and stab out both their eyes with a bread knife? Both are eligible, both are effective, yet both are so wrong. Let me explain:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Anyone whom watches anime deserves far worse than a knife hanging from each eye, they more accurately deserve intensive recovery to bring back the good within, which is NOT to watch anime and more time playing with the family pet or fighting over who should get breast fed first. This &amp;lsquo;alleged&amp;rsquo; procedure may involve unnecessary pain, taunting and possibly death, but at least they won&amp;rsquo;t be watching episode 456 of &amp;ldquo;This is hentai in the disguise of anime&amp;rdquo;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So what&amp;rsquo;s wrong with anime then? Absolutely everything if you ask me. It&amp;rsquo;s gay, It promotes anti-Semitic ideas and possibly fascism, just take a look at Bleach. In one of the alleged episodes, the main guy (with shit orange hair) gives a miscarried baby a back-hander in the face and shoves each arm into a separate incinerator and blender simultaneously, while forcing a young girl to listen to &amp;lsquo;my chemical romance&amp;rsquo;. In Sailor Moon, one of the girls in a tightly clad, yet visually illegal uniform, jumps out at another guy and gives him a &amp;lsquo;Dirty Sanchez&amp;rsquo;, although he probably isn&amp;rsquo;t straight!!!!! In Love Hina, one of the hot girls cannibalizes an other one of the other hot girls, without having sex with the dead corpse before hand. In Pokemon, Ash hands out &amp;lsquo;barely legal teen porn&amp;rsquo; to all his Pokemon, while he &amp;lsquo;feels-up&amp;rsquo; his entire family with a pair of tweezers and packet of gloves. So if you don&amp;rsquo;t call &amp;lsquo;that&amp;rsquo; wrong, then I DON&amp;rdquo;T KNOW WHAT IS.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Ok, so maybe i made up SOME aspects of my story, but not EVERY aspect, adding further truth and accuracy to my statement. So do you take the $50, or do you physically hurt them with your weak-like &amp;lsquo;skeletal&amp;rsquo; structure? Trick question people, you actually do both, although i don&amp;rsquo;t advise it, especially to my younger audience. Because remember kids, knifes are dangerous and should only be used as a form of cutlery, so unless if your going to eat him/her, you shouldn&amp;rsquo;t kill people with knifes!!!!! I personally, but allegedly find it a lot easier to kill people by paying other people to do it for you&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;..also known as a hitman. But if you can&amp;rsquo;t afford to pay for one, ask for another hitman to kill that hitman, which will be a never-ending cycle of death and happiness.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Julius Reade&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;rdquo; Knifes are cheaper, but guns are more effective. Take your pick and have fun*!!!!!!&amp;rdquo; &amp;ldquo;Please don&amp;rsquo;t kill anyone after reading this, especially the less-attractive. (Me)&amp;rdquo;&amp;ldquo;The straight joke involving Sailor Moon was supposed to be sarcasm, for any &amp;lsquo;slow people&amp;rsquo; out there.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The begining of a third generation</title>
      <link>https://juliusreade.com/sydneysucks/the-beginning-of-a-third-generation/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Jun 2008 18:02:30 +0934</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://juliusreade.com/sydneysucks/the-beginning-of-a-third-generation/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Some people would foolishly think that it would be really easy to write an article exploiting the reasons and issues behind &amp;lsquo;tea bagging&amp;rsquo;. But let me tell you, it&amp;rsquo;s not. Thought, dedication, commitment, rejection and other sexist ideas are bound together, before sucking in your entire face, killing all your relatives and such. However, I&amp;rsquo;m sure that there are many capable people out there with the ability to write articles without struggle. I&amp;rsquo;m not one of those people.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My ability to read is virtual non-existence; My limited attention span forces me to only socialise with my incredibly hot brother, before turning to my large collection of video games and porn; As with my constant habit to crave for an infinite line of cocaine at my disposal. Now many of my friends call my &amp;lsquo;drug habit&amp;rsquo; an addiction, but i tell them to get stuffed, just as i take another hit of heroin. It&amp;rsquo;s simply not true, just take a look at my usage. Allegedly, I only take a combination of Heroin and Cocaine 3 times each hour, which is absolutely nothing as compared to former personality, Darryl Summers and his habit for bad jokes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Not only have i taken this post to make a poor, but well-deserved Darryl Summers joke, but also for the new and slightly improved introduction to &amp;ldquo;Sydneysucks.blogspot.com&amp;rdquo;. I guess it&amp;rsquo;ll be my new domain to bitch about fat people and there tendency to eat, while us &amp;lsquo;normals&amp;rsquo; swim around in left-over scraps, hoping for a decent meal to eat&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So if you thought that the above statement was offensive, let it serve as a reminder, or let&amp;rsquo;s say &amp;lsquo;test&amp;rsquo; to the future content of this site/blog. If you were:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Heavily Offended: May i suggest that you hide in your closet, hoping that i won&amp;rsquo;t jump at you with a burning cross and cut your throat&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;with the burning cross???? WTF,,..?!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Slightly Offended: Quickly, turn off your computer and sell it to a Chinese man with a dodgy accent, before he sells it back to you for twice the retail value.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Slightly Amused: Then welcome!!!!! Please continue reading, as you&amp;rsquo;ll find that things are about to get a whole lot worse&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Heavily Amused: I spend hours on end writing these fking articles and&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;..wait a sec, oh sorry i thought this was &amp;ldquo;Heavily Offended&amp;rdquo;. I meant: Read the above comment.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So there you have it boys and girls. You either like me, hate me, or more accurately &amp;lsquo;Aren&amp;rsquo;t reading this&amp;rsquo;. How do i know? Over the period of my last blog i got 12 views from 3 months of dedication, which says a lot about the future of this blog and my success as a writer. But there is an upside. There&amp;rsquo;s simply no one to be offended, hopefully meaning a lesser chance i&amp;rsquo;ll get sued ;)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Julius Reade&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;Anyone thinking &amp;lsquo;WTF??. In other words, this blog was created as a successor of:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Melbournesucks.blogspot.com&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Adelaidesucks.blogpsot.com&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Have a closer look for more details. (Not advised for the &amp;lsquo;weak-hearted&amp;rsquo;)&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;I&amp;rsquo;ll admit that this article isn&amp;rsquo;t that good as compared to others, but it&amp;rsquo;s my first article for this blog, so I&amp;rsquo;m willing to pretend like it&amp;rsquo;s not such a big deal&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;PS: I don&amp;rsquo;t have an incredibly hot brother, let alone any siblings. Still leaving the question: Am i gay?&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>