<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Adelaidesucks-rsses on </title>
    <link>https://juliusreade.com/adelaidesucks/index.xml</link>
    <description>Recent content in Adelaidesucks-rsses on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>This work is licensed under a Creative Commons Attribution-ShareAlike 4.0 International License.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 26 Jan 2008 14:48:30 +0934</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://juliusreade.com/adelaidesucks/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>Petey Underground [Part 4]</title>
      <link>https://juliusreade.com/adelaidesucks/petey-underground-part-4/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Jan 2008 14:48:30 +0934</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://juliusreade.com/adelaidesucks/petey-underground-part-4/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Petey unlike other more fortunate children, wished and only dreamed of a normal life. Each day he would wake up to a world filled with concerned people facing him on the train, staring with evil thoughts, beyond his quirky smile and branded him as different. Minors stared diligently in caution at Petey, praying and hoping he wouldn&amp;rsquo;t merrily attack them with his rumored claws and fangs. Even teachers and peers unsurprisingly feared Petey with a certain type of hatred, that could not be broken, let alone seen before in somebody&amp;rsquo;s expression and dedication to hating Pete. Intensifying as the days past, teachers would often cane Petey for the most minimal of errors.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;Sorry sir&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;&amp;rdquo;, Petey whispered in a delusional voice. &amp;ldquo;I seriously didn&amp;rsquo;t mean it&amp;rdquo;. Petey knew he was in trouble, despite the harmless amount of disturbance he had accumulated.
&amp;ldquo;How dare you talk to an official persons of higher status than you in such an unworthy voice&amp;rdquo;, repeated the headmaster, who was also Petey&amp;rsquo;s teacher for that year. &amp;ldquo;You do know what this means&amp;rdquo;, The headmaster wearily said to the whole class. Petey gulped and took his final breath before pulling his gun out and shooting Headmaster between the eyes&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;..&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Despite hating his life Petey also feared the false evidence that somehow, somebody in his universe loved and enjoyed his company. It was something Petey had never truly experienced, but turned a blind eye on, as if it were impossible but knew that one day, he was going to meet someone who had a similar passion for death.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Julius Reade&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;I think I&amp;rsquo;ve made the point that Petey carries a gun a around with himself&amp;rdquo; (And that i can&amp;rsquo;t write)&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Still writing articles that make just as much sense as anime</title>
      <link>https://juliusreade.com/adelaidesucks/still-writing-articles-that-make-just-as-much-sense-as-anime/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jan 2008 12:33:30 +0934</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://juliusreade.com/adelaidesucks/still-writing-articles-that-make-just-as-much-sense-as-anime/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Stalking is an act which often gets bad press and media coverage world-wide, escpecially in western countries and societies. Not blaming our current media organizations for giving it an ever on-going bad image, but the fact that there simply isn&amp;rsquo;t enough coverage of stalking practices on tv and in social life. When much could be in fact done to help our small community of stalkers and child molesters, is either avoided or ignored by small-minded politicians whom believe little in creating a people and world of old but forgotten stalking traditions, when really these values are very helpful in terms of economic and capital prosperity.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Over the past few decades i have dedicated my life to try and help this so-called &amp;lsquo;sickness&amp;rsquo; within people, that i rather call a &amp;lsquo;gift&amp;rsquo;. But so can you with only the smallest of commitments that will make you feel good as a person and prevent the outcome that a child will not be molestered. Not to mention help the environment.*&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Are you sick of your children running around the house, causing amuck and knocking over antiques of high value? Well many of our facilities across America are in need of children for experimental purposes and are willing to pay reasonable amounts of money* to ensure that the pedophilia industry doesn&amp;rsquo;t go into bankruptcy and revert it&amp;rsquo;s savings into useless subjects, such as health care or education. We also assure that your children shall be in the greatest of care in our boarding house, filled with non-delicious fillers to make sure they grow up healthy and strong.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now many of our clients are concerned about the safety of their children and are worried with their well being in our facilities. From which i tell them, not to worry because under the guidance of our not-so-highly trained professionals and under graduates is the opportunity for your children to learn the possible secrets of the porn industry, as well be felt up and in some cases, fall pregnant. From which we skin your child in a terrifying way and sell the fetus to imported company&amp;rsquo;s such as Audi to be transfered to the nearest parts manufactured company to be processed.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There you have it. So remember next time when an old man with a dodgy look on his face snatches your child. Let him keep him/her as he&amp;rsquo;s sure to be supporting a worthy cause of large beneficial proportions. And what do you know, he might return it in one piece after he has &amp;lsquo;done his business&amp;rsquo;&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Julius Reade&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;and surprisingly no complaints&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;AS WITH FREAKIN&amp;rsquo; READERS!!!!!!!&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Threat of (my) piss-lame writing</title>
      <link>https://juliusreade.com/adelaidesucks/threat-of-my-piss-lame-writing/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Jan 2008 21:34:30 +0934</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://juliusreade.com/adelaidesucks/threat-of-my-piss-lame-writing/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;From outside my window lies the many drug dealers, murderers and possible scum that make up my neighborhood area. On my street alone, over 500 people have been killed, raped and killed again, in a constant battle to survive, mentally and physically. Even as higher authority within the suburb regions become ever so corrupt, a greater substance of evil reeks our streets and homes, with what only can be described as an increasingly common trend among the convenient and popular parts of greater colonies in Australia.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;An ever so common but dying trend, would immediately include the vast majority of people who teach their children about the prosperities of Islam and it&amp;rsquo;s teachings. Or to be put in simple terms, terrorism. Over 5 million people in Victoria alone are treated with some case of viable &amp;lsquo;rehab&amp;rsquo; solution to aid an increasing number of people from their past mishaps with the religion. But as evil and unexplainable as this seems, children from as young as 25 , have been dramatically affected from this cause of false hope.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Earlier, we interviewed drug-ridden child of 4 from Adelaide to try and capture his perspective on things. &amp;ldquo;Personally i think there&amp;rsquo;s a difference between &amp;lsquo;taking&amp;rsquo; drugs as compared to &amp;lsquo;doing&amp;rsquo; drugs. The spelling! Hahahaha&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;&amp;rdquo; (Laughs, before collapsing on the floor, as he slowly regurgitates and chokes his own vomit and saliva).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So from many years of dedicated research and preparation, does mankind discover that world-wide phenomena&amp;rsquo;s such as the attendant addiction of drugs, can be fixed through a combination of intense therapy and suicide, but to also eliminate the horrid thought of people on our streets that accumulate a bad reputation for our hookers and armed forces in disguise. Not to mention the greater and more important discovery that reading such articles as these is doing no good for you, or your brain.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Julius Reade&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;PS: Sorry for the bad joke about spelling. (Providing that anyone reads this crap?)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;If you thought this article was bad, read my Battle of the pacific review&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;..&amp;rdquo; (Let alone reading anything from this site/blog/piece of crap)&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Petey Underground [Part 2]</title>
      <link>https://juliusreade.com/adelaidesucks/petey-underground-part-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Jan 2008 21:36:30 +0934</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://juliusreade.com/adelaidesucks/petey-underground-part-2/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Petey&amp;rsquo;s constant urge to kill his closest ones, didn&amp;rsquo;t at all make him happy. No matter how little or big the situation, Petey would over exaggerate and kill his beloved in the most regretful of ways. Even after 10 years of his dreadful ways, he still hasn&amp;rsquo;t learnt the basics of respect for others, including himself. But there was a far deeper secret that was kept from anyone for many of years to come. For as we see, Petey is not human. He is far more complex and ruthless. Unfortunately, Petey had to find it out the hard way&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;.and it all happened when he was a child.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;Hey mate, pass me the ball&amp;rdquo;, Petey shouted to his best know friend.
&amp;ldquo;Fuck you, and I&amp;rsquo;m not your mate&amp;rdquo;, He replied. But despite the swearing, this was the usual answer Petey received from his school mates. Not only did this make him sad, but frustrated inside.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;C&amp;rsquo;mon mate just give me a kick, you&amp;rsquo;ve had the ball the whole time&amp;rdquo;, Petey asked again. This time however, Tim stopped, as did his other friends.
&amp;ldquo;That&amp;rsquo;s it Petey, I&amp;rsquo;m sick and tired of your fucking whining and being gay, so fucking stop it!!!! You shouldn&amp;rsquo;t even be hanging out with us in the first place.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;But the teacher said&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;&amp;rdquo;, Petey said as tears slowly poured out of his eyes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;I don&amp;rsquo;t give a fuck what the teacher said. The fact is, we don&amp;rsquo;t like you and no one else will, so FUCK.OFF!!!!!!&amp;rdquo;, Tim aggressively shouted, as Petey ran off in tears, wondering what to do with his life.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Then suddenly, Petey regained confidence. He felt good, like never before, like nothing could stop him. Unfortunately, this would mean the turning point in his long and yet to be worse life.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;Oi, fuck head&amp;rdquo;, Petey screamed at Tim, as all his friends stared in surprise at Petey. &amp;ldquo;Just watch out next time, i don&amp;rsquo;t want you to hurt your pretty little face&amp;rdquo;. Petey knew he had stirred something up in Tim&amp;rsquo;s mind.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;What the fuck!? If you think your so tough, why don&amp;rsquo;t you come over here and say that&amp;rdquo;, Tim smartly said, as he knew it would be easier to bash up Petey with more support.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;Sorry, don&amp;rsquo;t want to look like a prick near you guys.&amp;rdquo; and it was this line that made Tim wildly charge at Petey with all his might&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;..But before Tim could reach Petey, something indefinitely stopped him from Reaching the weak pile of skin and bone ahead of him.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Petey pulled out a .45 handgun from his hidden pocket, closed his eyes and randomly shot at the incoming shadow as quickly as his finger would let him. Not being able to see though, Petey knew he had hit something, when his shots corresponded to the loud and expected screams from Tim. But the screaming soon stopped, and as Petey re-open his eyes to see what he had done, a corpse of his former-enemy lay only metres from where he was standing. But Petey had no where to run. He knew he would be punished to an extreme&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;.However, for the first time in his life, Petey felt the happiest he had ever been, and even a bit proud for himself&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Julius Reade&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;Don&amp;rsquo;t bother to ask me where he got the gun from, cause HE JUST HAD IT!!!!!!!&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Petey Underground</title>
      <link>https://juliusreade.com/adelaidesucks/petey-underground/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Jan 2008 21:18:01 +0934</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://juliusreade.com/adelaidesucks/petey-underground/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;What the hell??&amp;rdquo;, Petey shouted as he carefully examined the room, while discovering that his wife was sleeping with another woman.
&amp;ldquo;Whats the matter&amp;rdquo; Jenny said, as she turned on the bedside lamp.
&amp;ldquo;Your sleeping with another woman for Fucking sake!!!!&amp;rdquo;, Petey angrily claimed.
&amp;ldquo;So? It&amp;rsquo;s not like I&amp;rsquo;ve broken the law or anything&amp;rdquo;, she answered.
&amp;ldquo;But, But, But, But&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;.&amp;rdquo;, Petey was speechless. &amp;ldquo;I don&amp;rsquo;t know what to say. I thought you loved me but that doesn&amp;rsquo;t seem to be the case. You disgust me&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;&amp;rdquo;, Petey left the room in immense sadness.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;Well what a Cunt he is tha&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;..&amp;rdquo;, but before she could finish her sentence, a knife of sharp properties came flying through the air, before it pierced her skull, which caused it to collapse into a pile of dead flesh and brain.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;How do you like that bitch!!!!&amp;rdquo;, Petey exclaimed, over the screaming of the other woman in bed. It was a scream of High pitch like in many of the fictional horror movies ever so often. But unlike the one in the movies, this one pissed Petey off.
&amp;ldquo;Shut the fuck up and get over it!!!!&amp;rdquo; Petey shouted at the widow in his torn bed&amp;hellip;. &amp;ldquo;I don&amp;rsquo;t think she can hear me&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;&amp;rdquo;, Petey whispered, as he left the room in search for a lighter and an alcohol beverage. Petey&amp;rsquo;s idea of a &amp;lsquo;solution&amp;rsquo; usually meant the instant death of a person or rather the permanent torture of his victims.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;Sorry bout before&amp;rdquo; Petey apologized, as he re-entered the room. But the reaction wasn&amp;rsquo;t too pleasant.
&amp;ldquo;Get the Fuck out of here you murderer&amp;rdquo;, the not-so-kind woman screamed Directly at Petey.
&amp;ldquo;Wrong answer, bitch&amp;rdquo;, Petey replied, as he immediately lit the molotov cocktail. Then &amp;ldquo;Boom!&amp;rdquo;&amp;lsquo;, the apartment room of Petey&amp;rsquo;s residence blew to pieces, slightly before the whole block set-ablaze.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One by one, people jumped out of their apartment windows, for a plead of survival. Petey however, was siting quietly on a park bench, slowly recovering from his quick and undetermined escape, quietly staring at his &amp;ldquo;once&amp;rdquo; apartment block deteriorate into smoke, just as if nothing had happened&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Julius Reade&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;Tell your **** sister to ***** her ***** life which ******* can go ******* my ******* under the table&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rove: The script they didn&#39;t play to air.</title>
      <link>https://juliusreade.com/adelaidesucks/rove-the-script-they-didnt-play-to-air./</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Jan 2008 13:33:30 +0934</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://juliusreade.com/adelaidesucks/rove-the-script-they-didnt-play-to-air./</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Ransom was a very unusual name for the Greek child from Athens. All day long he would dream about the promises that one day, he like everybody else had a normal name. Unlike his name though, Ransom lived a very fulfilling life, often par-taking in seasonal trips to many destinations around the world. However, a far darker secret kept Ransom from discovering the true reasoning behind his name. A secret much more evil and terrifying than the Japanese and their effect on the world&amp;rsquo;s anime-liking population&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Which thankfully brings me to the question, why am i so popular within the Muslim community? Or more importantly, how i became to be the worlds greatest leader of much intelligence and popularity? Sure you could say I&amp;rsquo;m actually a murderer and perfected scam artist that has impressively killed many innocent people from my many inspiring looks and inner integrity. But why be negative in our current world where worrying about the simplest of problems has become our utter and foremost number one priority? Too bad for you, that many of your peers (Including your relatives and best friends) most-likely despise your existence to make themselves feel bigger than they really are. Not to mention that your face reeks of polluting lotion only found in the Serbian desert and that your unrequired ugliness can&amp;rsquo;t be fixed no matter how hard you scrape the burning tar off your face&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;..Uh?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But don&amp;rsquo;t fear, as the tar on your face is most likely a substitute for your Ritalin, which we all know; IS ONLY GOING TO MAKE IT WORSE. (Rove&amp;rsquo;s audience laughs).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Julius Reade&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;Desperation is the only reason to be abuse cute animals&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;.like the giraffe&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I hate anime.............. [Part 4]</title>
      <link>https://juliusreade.com/adelaidesucks/i-hate-anime..............-part-4/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Jan 2008 14:41:30 +0934</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://juliusreade.com/adelaidesucks/i-hate-anime..............-part-4/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The understanding of Global law and life has gradually helped/forced people to learn the essentials of living, including the way we eat, sleep and move. Even the smallest things such as our law not to kill others has taught us that killing other people is bad and often unacceptable. Other practices have also taught us much more to the understanding of life.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When a fan of anime attempts to talk to us normal people for example, we must look carefully at their tag number and their condition of previous brain washing. As humans, we all know that anime fans have been programmed for evil and have public tag numbers, in case of malfunction. In such cases, when the anime fan is trying to communicate to an &amp;ldquo;outsider&amp;rdquo; i.e &amp;lsquo;you&amp;rsquo;, we must stand at least 2 metres away from the person to ensure your safety and mental sanity, (No one likes to here people talking about anime, let alone watch it). Then immediately try and identify the tag number* from as far away as possible, while keeping your ears blocked at all times, to try and minimize the possible noise from the mentally insane person. The number will then used to hand over to government personnel to take the situation into further precaution. But what if the anime fan is a newer model that doesn&amp;rsquo;t display the tag number?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When in the case that the fanatic is a newer model (pre-2006), be sure to have your cell phone pre-dialed on your country&amp;rsquo;s national security hotline number, to be ready to call and alert further authority of the current situation. Don&amp;rsquo;t have a mobile phone? Then now has never been a better time as the threat of an anime invasion is imminent, escpecially in Japan and in many parts around the world.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So there you have it. Remember next time when you meet someone that likes anime, be sure to have your stabbing knife out and a pre-dialed cellphone. (I&amp;rsquo;ll explain the stabbing bit in Part 5)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Julius Reade&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Note*: The tag number is usually located on the neck, however it will be fairly clear when you see the person.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;Guitar Hero3 has consumed my life like a really good book&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;..Which isn&amp;rsquo;t much then i guess?&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cover it: Correction fluid</title>
      <link>https://juliusreade.com/adelaidesucks/cover-it-correction-fluid/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Dec 2007 10:49:30 +0934</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://juliusreade.com/adelaidesucks/cover-it-correction-fluid/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;In todays society people remain prone to terrorist attacks and thoughts of the liking. Everyday millions of people are out on the streets waiting to be car bombed or possibly be taken hostage by serial killers and gang rapists. Just recently, a family of six were killed by a mob of people for not speaking English. Many or possibly a majority believe that &amp;lsquo;risk&amp;rsquo; is a factor to be blamed. Drugs and freedom are also to be blamed as a quick response to the issue. Police are already undercover trying their hardest to reveal the crime syndicates behind the attacks and further menaces to society. But what can we do as a people to try and keep such people from harming our neutral way of life?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Expert Socialist, Tim Regan yet again proved that you can protect your family from terrorists with just a few hundred dollars and a couple of household appliances, although he was reluctant to offer any information. So us at the channel 6 news team decided to make up our own:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Convert to Islam - Would terrorists attack their own kind? Of course not* but remember that you don&amp;rsquo;t really believe in their faith. Seriously.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Wear a robe - People know that the stereotypical Muslim/evil dictator wears a robe of some sort, now so can you. With a couple of bed sheets and bath towels, you too can look like Osama or celebrity dictator, Saddam Hussein.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Pre-install a bomb inside your car - Everybody knows that a terrorists no. 1# target is the humble car/vehicle. So why not eliminate the threat and install the bomb before hand, so that the terrorists have 100% no chance to do the dirty work :)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Alert people about the threat of terrorism - Why not gather a few friends and spread the word that terrorism is out there to kill you. Engulf peaceful communities into fear ridden people who embrace loneliness within their lives as a way of keeping safe. Or even better. Demonstrate the dangers of terrorism to small and vulnerable children with live theater acts based on real-time death re-enactments of people in the Iraq War&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So there you have it. Within 1-2 weeks you and your family can be safe from most threats including herpes, the flu and Chinese people. Just remember that drugs only hurt if you over dose.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Julius Reade&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;rdquo; Page up to be certain, Page from up to be happy from those who care&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Reading is the no. 1# source of death in the USA *</title>
      <link>https://juliusreade.com/adelaidesucks/reading-is-the-no.-1</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Dec 2007 19:48:30 +0934</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://juliusreade.com/adelaidesucks/reading-is-the-no.-1</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;As a former reader, i was confused and worried about myself and the amount of reading i was doing. That was until my doctor told me that i was reading dangerous amounts, exceeding the 4 books a year limit. Which is why i decided to stop reading altogether. But why read? It only benefits us in the most dramatic of ways and most likely will improve our range of vocabulary. Even our teachers encourage us to read and learn to improve our former selfs. So i say, Refuse, Annoy and Take drugs.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;Refuse&amp;rdquo;, what my parents once told me as a child when confronting against strangers and pedophiles. So as a teacher or &amp;lsquo;smart person&amp;rsquo; approaches, simply refuse their request to read, learn or interact with their language of choice. But as we all know, I&amp;rsquo;d rather respond to a teacher than cop a suspension. Which is why we move on to the second step.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Annoy. I really should have thought more carefully about my choices because annoying the teacher would only make the situation worse. Damn it. Just move on to the third step.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Take drugs etc. Now after you&amp;rsquo;ve been suspended from your school due to &amp;lsquo;unresponsive reasons&amp;rsquo; (assuming that you&amp;rsquo;re a retard), you might want to take up drugs, smoking or a combination to help &amp;lsquo;sober up&amp;rsquo; from all your mishaps. Trust me, it works&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So now that you feel much happier with yourself and life in general, you may begin to feel a sight urge of regret in your life and possibly, &amp;lsquo;turn against yourself&amp;rsquo;. But as far as suicide and cutting your wrists go, there are more important things in life instead of dying. Unfortunately i haven&amp;rsquo;t written a guide for it and probably never will. Oh well, at least you lived a good life with a Dependant and loving family. If you didn&amp;rsquo;t, you probably spent half your lonely day, figuring out possible death routes for favored low-life Darryl Summers&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Julius Reade&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;My apologies to the woman at Knox shopping centre who i defamed in front of the public eye. Suggesting that i was &amp;lsquo;too fat&amp;rsquo; for a session of paintball shooting&amp;rdquo;.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Underwood series....................</title>
      <link>https://juliusreade.com/adelaidesucks/the-underwood-series..................../</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Dec 2007 19:48:30 +0934</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://juliusreade.com/adelaidesucks/the-underwood-series..................../</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Everyday i begin my morning with a chilled glass of milk and a couple of fish fingers. From which i work my way to a clean bowl of fruit with extra raisins. Not to be confused with my favorite dish, a banquette of spaghetti and possible combinations of dried up apple core and skin to create the perfect treat. Sometimes i even enjoy eating the quirkiest of recipes including mashed banana with butter and crumpled pear indulged in the bones of a crushed wallaby. Who knows what other methods of torture we could introduce to our recipes of choice. Stabbing was an option that never seemed to pick up in popularity. But more importantly i mostly enojy eating meat which is why i introduce: The Underwood Series&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;..&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Last night i was lucky enough to treat my taste buds to the many flavors and body parts of lamb and cow limbs. In a boost of happiness i attempted to take a bite into the lamb ear, until the door bell rang and interrupted my meal.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In immediate frustration i ignored the door and ran to my bathroom cupboard, searching for some Viagra to try and keep me calm. But the door kept ringing. In anticipation i shouted, &amp;ldquo; Shut the f**k up!!!&amp;rdquo; in as loud and racist voice as i could. The ringing stopped, but in replacement a child-like cry was heard. Now i was pissed off.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In a further attempt to try and put an end to the noise i decided to throw household objects at the door. With my careless attitude i picked up my printer and threw it at the door. My neighbors must of thought i was crazy with the occasional &amp;lsquo;Crash&amp;rsquo; and &amp;lsquo;Bang&amp;rsquo; noise streaming from my house.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One by one i threw things at the door. The Lamp, bowls, boxes of cereal, were all thrown until a point where there was nothing to throw. But the crying noise would not stop. But i felt calmed.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I don&amp;rsquo;t know what it was but i felt better ever since i had completely destroyed my furnishings.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I had decided that it was time to open the door and confront whom ever was outside.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thoughts then began accumulating in my head. What if it was criminal, or even worse; a murderer!? I dropped to the floor in fear and anxiety.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I couldn&amp;rsquo;t feel my feet any more. It soon affected my legs; secondly my arms; then my body; until i couldn&amp;rsquo;t feel anything. I felt&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;.numb. I felt like crying&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;but couldn&amp;rsquo;t. What was wrong with me&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;..&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Julius Reade&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;rdquo; Hopefully there isn&amp;rsquo;t another series called {The Underwood series} &amp;ldquo;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rock and Roll Adventures: Review</title>
      <link>https://juliusreade.com/adelaidesucks/rock-and-roll-adventures-review/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Dec 2007 11:02:30 +0934</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://juliusreade.com/adelaidesucks/rock-and-roll-adventures-review/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;As a sign of gratitude, my friends decided to buy a pre-owned version of &amp;ldquo;Rock and Roll Adventures&amp;rdquo; for $30 at JB-Hifi (For Wii). But as nice as that sounds&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;.the game is basicly shit. The graphics are worse than my GBA emulator and there&amp;rsquo;s enough replay value to last you 5 hours of boredom. So why did i play this game? Or possibly a better question: What kind of drugs was i taking when i played the game? But i did eventually finish it&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The game starts off with you (Or in this case ME) playing a graphically challenged character in the form of an imitation of Elvis. The main objective of the game is to attack evil instruments&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;but why? Maybe if i had paid more attention to the game and not the floor i would have actually understood how crap it was!!!!&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;F**k it. Just don&amp;rsquo;t buy it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Graphics: 0/10 - Can&amp;rsquo;t remember. I spent too much time miming the word &amp;ldquo;death&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;Kill me&amp;rdquo;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Sound: 0/10 - Put my TV on mute to minimalise boredom.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Gameplay: 0/10 - Don&amp;rsquo;t be ridiculous&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Lasting Appeal: &lt;sup&gt;5&lt;/sup&gt;&amp;frasl;&lt;sub&gt;10&lt;/sub&gt; - Boy was it fun when i put the disk into the shredder&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;..repeatedly.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Article worthy: &lt;sup&gt;10&lt;/sup&gt;&amp;frasl;&lt;sub&gt;10&lt;/sub&gt; - What do you think this is?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Rating 2.3&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Overall it was definitely more of a prank than a gift&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Julius Reade&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;Christmas is a time for giving, taking and forgetting the first step&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I hate anime.............. [Part 3]</title>
      <link>https://juliusreade.com/adelaidesucks/i-hate-anime..............-part-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Dec 2007 14:17:30 +0934</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://juliusreade.com/adelaidesucks/i-hate-anime..............-part-3/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The average day of my life consists of:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;5 hours of Smash Bros.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;3 solid hours of Smash Bros.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;4 hours thinking about Time Splitters 2&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Remaining time used to cover myself in fragment Lotion and Pasta Sauce.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;..which begs the question&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;what do i hate? (anime)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Answer: Anime. But Why?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Or perhaps we should be asking real questions like:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why is anime so shit?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Does any one care beside me?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But aside the point, i decided to look further into this issue through meditation and ancient methods of healing. But did it work? Not really, but i did learn a lot about the many &amp;ldquo;Victims&amp;rdquo; of past anime addicts and former freaks. Tara Mingle, whom did not want to be named, claimed that her anime addiction was horrible and scary. She even said that anime has exposed her to a lifetime of constant pain and suffering. Fortunately however, she died later that evening of an unknown cause. Possibly because i shot her in the head. But remember. Guns don&amp;rsquo;t kill people. Death does.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;rdquo; I never really had no computer, i just couldn&amp;rsquo;t be stuffed doing this&amp;rdquo;&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hey Hey Hey</title>
      <link>https://juliusreade.com/adelaidesucks/hey-hey-hey/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Dec 2007 21:25:30 +0934</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://juliusreade.com/adelaidesucks/hey-hey-hey/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;No computer = No articles :)&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Super Paper Mario Review</title>
      <link>https://juliusreade.com/adelaidesucks/super-paper-mario-review/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Nov 2007 20:53:30 +0934</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://juliusreade.com/adelaidesucks/super-paper-mario-review/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;,Looking back at all the articles (Mine you idiot), i found a lot of mistakes that made me go WTF? Such as incomplete sentences and. But also a lot of words missing. But as myself, i didn&amp;rsquo;t take the time to fix the mistakes, that potentially were quite obvious and &amp;ldquo;unique&amp;rdquo;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;However, we gather in the woods today, to listen to to one of my reviews around the warm camp fire, that ironically begins in the couch of my living room.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The main reason why i played Super Paper Mario, was based upon the fact that i &amp;ldquo;Received&amp;rdquo; it for free, one way or another. But aside the point, the game deserves to be scrapped by all means of the imagination. It&amp;rsquo;s crappy design adds to further frustration when trying to complete levels, which can be annoying at times. Even basic controls have been ruined, with the developers decision to use one button to play the entire campaign. But worst of all would have to be the $400 recommended price.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now for $400 you can buy:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Anime dvd&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Drugs&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&amp;ldquo;Adopt&amp;rdquo; a child (Slave)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;OR&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Super Paper Mario&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With my first preference being the Anime dvd (Shit&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;..wrong answer), I think we can all agree that Super Paper Mario is a poor game, with the lowest of standards for a 2-D Platformer on the the Wii.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Cons:                       Pros:
-Everything               - Nothing to see here&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Rating: 9.1&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Julius Reade&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It never matters what the hell you write in a review, people only bother to check the overall rating, with this article as an exception. (No one reads this crap)&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Non-Update #4</title>
      <link>https://juliusreade.com/adelaidesucks/non-update-</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Nov 2007 10:53:30 +0934</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://juliusreade.com/adelaidesucks/non-update-</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Just want to say that looking back at previous articles, i have found some really f**ked up mistakes, that made sentences make no sense what-so ever. ( I really should re-read what i write).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Some mistakes include:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Sentences that mean and make no sense&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Missing words from sentences&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;VERY badly planned sentences&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Not writing enough articles based on hating anime&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Mario Galaxy - 56 stars&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>